
<records>
  <rec resultID="1">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3387827">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Word and Sentence Prosody : The Endangered Dialect of Koshikijima Japanese</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Haruo Kubozono</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Phonology and Phonetics</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110735055</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110730074</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110730128</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00031</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter Mouton</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Word and Sentence Prosody : The Endangered Dialect of Koshikijima Japanese</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Haruo Kubozono</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / Phonetics &amp; Phonology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Endangered languages--Japan--Koshiki Islands</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Japanese language--Versification</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Japanese language--Dialects</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This is the first comprehensive work on word and sentence prosody in Koshikijima Japanese, a dialect of Japanese not fully documented in the literature. It is an endangered dialect spoken by about 2,000 speakers on a small southern island in Japan. Being separated from mainland dialects by the sea, this dialect exhibits unique prosodic features not shared by other Japanese dialects. It also exhibits considerable regional variations among the ten or more small villages that were isolated from each other until recently.Based on the author's fieldwork, the book analyzes word accent and intonation, the two linguistic areas in which this endangered dialect exhibits unique features and remarkable regional variations within itself. They include the emergence and development of a secondary H tone, postlexical deletion of the primary H tone, and the L boundary tone in question and vocative intonation. These phenomena bear crucially on general issues in prosody, including postlexical tonal neutralizations, competitions between lexical and postlexical tones, and the number of tones that a syllable can maximally bear. The book thus demonstrates the relevance of studying an endangered language/dialect in general linguistic contexts.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3387827&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="2">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3387808">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Language and Emotion. Volume 2</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Gesine Lenore Schiewer</au>
            <au>Jeanette Altarriba</au>
            <au>Bee Chin Ng</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Language and Emotion</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110670783</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110670851</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110670882</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00002</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter Mouton</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Language and Emotion. Volume 2</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Gesine Lenore Schiewer</au>
            <au>Jeanette Altarriba</au>
            <au>Bee Chin Ng</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Communication</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Language and emotions</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Emotive (Linguistics)</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Die Reihe HANDBÜCHER ZUR SPRACH- UND KOMMUNIKATIONSWISSENSCHAFT erschließt einen Wissensbereich, der sowohl die allgemeine Linguistik und die speziellen, philologisch orientierten Sprachwissenschaften als auch diejenigen Wissenschaftsgebiete umfasst, die sich in den letzten Jahrzehnten aus der immer umfangreicher werdenden Forschung über die vielfältigen Erscheinungen des kommunikativen Handelns entwickelt haben. In der klassischen Disziplin der Sprachwissenschaft erscheint eine Zusammenfassung des Wissensstandes notwendig, um der im Wechsel der Theorien rasch voranschreitenden Forschung eine Bezugsbasis zu geben; in den neuen Wissenschaften können die Handbücher dem Forscher Übersicht geben und Orientierung verschaffen. Um diese Ziele zu erreichen, wird in der Handbuchreihe, was die Vollständigkeit in der Darstellung, die Explizitheit in der Begründung, die Verlässlichkeit in der Dokumentation von Daten und Ergebnissen und die Aktualität im Methodischenangeht, eine Stufe der Verwirklichung angestrebt, die mit den besten Handbuchkonzeptionen anderer Wissenschaftszweige vergleichbar ist. Alle Herausgeber, die der Reihe und diejenigen der einzelnen Bände, wie auch alle Autoren, die in den Handbüchern ein Thema bearbeiten, tragen dazu bei, dieses Ziel zu verwirklichen. Veröffentlichungssprache ist Englisch. Wenngleich als Hauptzweck der Handbuchreihe die angemessene Darstellung des derzeitigen Wissensstandes in den durch die jeweiligen Handbuchbände abgedeckten Ausschnitten der Sprach- und Kommunikationswissenschaft zu gelten hat, so wird doch bei der Abgrenzung der wissenschaftlichen Bereiche, die jeweils in einem Handbuchband erschlossen werden sollen, keine starre Systematik vorausgesetzt. Die Reihe ist offen; die geschichtliche Entwicklung kann berücksichtigt werden. Diese Konzeption sowie die Notwendigkeit, dass zur gründlichen Vorbereitung jedes Bandes genügend Zeit zur Verfügung steht, führen dazu, dass die ganze Reihe in loser Erscheinungsfolge ihrer Bände vervollständigt werden kann. Jeder Band ist ein in sich abgeschlossenes Werk. Die Reihenfolge der Handbuchbände stellt keine Gewichtung der Bereiche dar, sondern hat sich durch die Art der Organisation ergeben: die Herausgeber der Reihe bemühen sich, eine Kollegin oder einen Kollegen für die Herausgabe eines Handbuchbandes zu gewinnen. Hat diese/r zugesagt, so ist sie/er in der Wahl der Mitherausgeber und bei der Einladung der Autoren vollkommen frei. Die Herausgeber eines Bandes planen einen Band inhaltlich unabhängig und werden dabei lediglich an bestimmte Prinzipien für den Aufbau und die Abfassung gebunden; nur wo es um die Abgrenzung zu anderen Bänden geht, sind die Reihenherausgeber inhaltlich beteiligt. Dabei wird davon ausgegangen, dass mit dieser Organisationsform der Hauptzweck dieser Handbuchreihe, nämlich die angemessene Darstellung des derzeitigen Problem- und Wissensstandes in den durch die jeweiligen Handbuchbände abgedeckten Teilbereichen, am besten verwirklicht werden kann.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3387808&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="3">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3377023">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Research Anthology on Medical Informatics in Breast and Cervical Cancer</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Information Resources Management Association</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781668471364</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668471371</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668471388</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Medical Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Research Anthology on Medical Informatics in Breast and Cervical Cancer</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Information Resources Management Association</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Oncology / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">HEALTH &amp; FITNESS / Women's Health</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Informatics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Medical informatics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Cervix uteri--Cancer--Diagnosis</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Breast--Cancer--Diagnosis</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Cancer research is currently a vital field of study as it affects a wide range of the population either directly or indirectly. Breast and cervical cancer are two prevalent types that pose a threat to women's health and wellness. Due to this, further research on the importance of medical informatics within this field is necessary to ensure patients receive the best possible attention and care. The Research Anthology on Medical Informatics in Breast and Cervical Cancer provides current research and information on how medical informatics are utilized within the field of breast and cervical cancer and considers the best practices and challenges of its implementation. Covering key topics such as women's health, wellness, oncology, and patient care, this major reference work is ideal for medical professionals, nurses, oncologists, policymakers, researchers, academicians, scholars, practitioners, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3377023&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="4">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3347603">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Public Innovation and Digital Transformation</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Hannele Väyrynen</au>
            <au>Nina Helander</au>
            <au>Harri Jalonen</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Routledge Studies in Innovation, Organizations and Technology</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781032137414</isbn>
          <isbn type="print">9781032137971</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781000686371</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781000686432</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781003230854</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Routledge</pub>
          <place>Abingdon, Oxon</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Public Innovation and Digital Transformation</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Hannele Väyrynen</au>
            <au>Nina Helander</au>
            <au>Harri Jalonen</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / Economic Development</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Organizational Development</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Public administration--Data processing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Public administration--Technological innovations</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Technological innovations--Management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Public-private sector cooperation</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Public innovation and digitalization are reshaping organizations and society in various ways and within multiple fields, as innovations are essential in transforming our world and addressing global sustainability and development challenges. This book addresses the fascinating relationship of these two contemporary topics and explores the role of digital transformation in promoting public innovation. This edited collection includes examples of innovations that emerge suddenly, practices for processing innovations, and the requirements for transformation from innovation to the'new normal'. Acknowledging that public innovation refers to the development and realization of new and creative ideas that challenge conventional wisdom and disrupt the established practices within a specific context, expert contributions from international scholars explore and illustrate the various activities that are happening in the world of multiple digitalization opportunities. The content covers public administration, technical and business management, human, social, and future sciences, paying attention to the interaction between public and private sectors to utilize digitalization in order to facilitate public innovation. This timely book will be of interest to researchers, academics and students in the fields of technology and innovation management, as well as knowledge management, public service management and administration.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3347603&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="5">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3414006">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Supplier for Hitler's War : The Continental Group During the Nazi Period</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Paul Erker</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9783110642193</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110642551</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110646436</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>De Gruyter Oldenbourg</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Supplier for Hitler's War : The Continental Group During the Nazi Period</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Paul Erker</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Industries / Automobile Industry</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">HISTORY / Europe / Germany</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">HISTORY / Social History</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">World War, 1939-1945--Germany</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Aircraft supplies industry--Germany--History--20th century</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Automobile supplies industry--Germany--History--20th century</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This study is the first to comprehensively examine the development of the Continental rubber and tire company during the Nazi period using sources that have recently become available. It shows to which extent Continental developed into a model Nazi operation within the scope of the National Socialist autarky, armaments, and war economy and analyzes how it dealt with foreign workers and activities in occupied, allied, and neutral countries.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3414006&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="6">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3358219">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Cases on Teaching English for Academic Purposes (EAP) During COVID-19 : Insights From Around the World</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Lucas Kohnke</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781668441480</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668441503</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668441510</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Cases on Teaching English for Academic Purposes (EAP) During COVID-19 : Insights From Around the World</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Lucas Kohnke</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Study &amp; Teaching</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">EDUCATION / Schools / Levels / Higher</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">EDUCATION / Teaching / Subjects / Language Arts</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">English language--Study and teaching (Higher)--Computer-assisted instruction for foreign speakers</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">English language--Study and teaching (Higher)--Foreign speakers</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">COVID-19 Pandemic, 2020---Social aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Web-based instruction</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The COVID-19 outbreak has changed the educational landscape as higher education institutions around the world were forced to close their physical campuses to slow or contain the spread of the virus. The rapid, unexpected, and forced transition to emergency remote teaching has been especially challenging for second- and foreign-language learners who rely on English for Academic Purposes (EAP) courses to help them transition from secondary school to higher education and succeed in their academic studies. To ensure these learners are receiving the best education possible, additional study on the difficulties, opportunities, and strategies of teaching English for Academic Purposes courses is required. Cases on Teaching English for Academic Purposes (EAP) During COVID-19: Insights From Around the World explores the effect of emergency remote teaching in offering quality EAP education to second- and foreign-language students and preparing them for their university studies in response to COVID-19 from a variety of contexts around the world. This book also contributes to developing effective practices for supporting and sustaining EAP teaching in an English-medium instruction environment during and after a pandemic. Covering topics such as remote teaching, writing instruction, and breakout rooms, this reference work is ideal for teachers, administrators, policymakers, scholars, practitioners, academicians, researchers, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3358219&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="7">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3321891">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>RNA, the Epicenter of Genetic Information</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>John Mattick</au>
            <au>Paulo Amaral</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9780367567781</isbn>
          <isbn type="print">9780367623920</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781000623086</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781000623116</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781003109242</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <ed>First edition</ed>
          <pub>CRC Press</pub>
          <place>Boca Raton</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>RNA, the Epicenter of Genetic Information</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>John Mattick</au>
            <au>Paulo Amaral</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Molecular Biology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Biochemistry</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Biology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Biophysics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Biotechnology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Organic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Cell Biology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Genetics &amp; Genomics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Microbiology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Virology</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">RNA</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Molecular biology--History</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Genomes</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The origin story and emergence of molecular biology is muddled. The early triumphs in bacterial genetics and the complexity of animal and plant genomes complicate an intricate history. This book documents the many advances, as well as the prejudices and founder fallacies. It highlights the premature relegation of RNA to simply an intermediate between gene and protein, the underestimation of the amount of information required to program the development of multicellular organisms, and the dawning realization that RNA is the cornerstone of cell biology, development, brain function and probably evolution itself. Key personalities, their hubris as well as prescient predictions are richly illustrated with quotes, archival material, photographs, diagrams and references to bring the people, ideas and discoveries to life, from the conceptual cradles of molecular biology to the current revolution in the understanding of genetic information. Key Features Documents the confused early history of DNA, RNA and proteins - a transformative history of molecular biology like no other. Integrates the influences of biochemistry and genetics on the landscape of molecular biology. Chronicles the important discoveries, preconceptions and misconceptions that retarded or misdirected progress. Highlights major pioneers and contributors to molecular biology, with a focus on RNA and noncoding DNA. Summarizes the mounting evidence for the central roles of non-protein-coding RNA in cell and developmental biology. Provides a thought-provoking retrospective and forward-looking perspective for advanced students and professional researchers. The Open Access version of this book, available at www.taylorfrancis.com, has been made available under a Creative Commons Attribution-Non Commercial-No Derivatives 4.0 license.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3321891&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="8">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3394223">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Binominal Lexemes in Cross-Linguistic Perspective : Towards a Typology of Complex Lexemes</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Steve Pepper</au>
            <au>Francesca Masini</au>
            <au>Simone Mattiola</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Empirical Approaches to Language Typology</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110640878</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110673494</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110673524</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00062</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter Mouton</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Binominal Lexemes in Cross-Linguistic Perspective : Towards a Typology of Complex Lexemes</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Steve Pepper</au>
            <au>Francesca Masini</au>
            <au>Simone Mattiola</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Grammar, Comparative and general</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The typological, contrastive, and descriptive studies in this volume investigate the strategies employed by the world's languages to create complex denotations by combining two noun-like elements, together with the kinds of semantic relation they involve, and their acquisition by children. The term ‘binominal lexeme'is employed to cover both noun-noun compounds and a range of other naming strategies, including prepositional compounds, relational compounds, construct forms, genitival constructions, and more. Overall, the volume suggests a new, cross-linguistic approach to the study of complex lexeme formation that cuts across the traditional boundaries between syntax, morphology, and lexicon.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3394223&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="9">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3394224">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Quantitative Approaches to Universality and Individuality in Language</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Makoto Yamazaki</au>
            <au>Haruko Sanada</au>
            <au>Reinhard Köhler</au>
            <au>Sheila Embleton</au>
            <au>Relja Vulanović</au>
            <au>Eric S. Wheeler</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Quantitative Linguistics</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110628081</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110763560</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110763638</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00075</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter Mouton</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Quantitative Approaches to Universality and Individuality in Language</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Makoto Yamazaki</au>
            <au>Haruko Sanada</au>
            <au>Reinhard Köhler</au>
            <au>Sheila Embleton</au>
            <au>Relja Vulanović</au>
            <au>Eric S. Wheeler</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Linguistic universals</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Comparative linguistics</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Founding Editor: Gabriel Altmann The series Quantitative Linguistics publishes books on all aspects of quantitative methods and models in linguistics, text analysis and related research fields. Specifically, the scope of the series covers the whole spectrum of theoretical and empirical research, ultimately striving for an exact mathematical formulation and empirical testing of hypotheses: observation and description of linguistic data, application of methods and models, discussion of methodological and epistemological issues, modelling of language and text phenomena.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3394224&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="10">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3366045">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Managing Inflation and Supply Chain Disruptions in the Global Economy</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Ulas Akkucuk</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Logistics, Operations, and Management Science (ALOMS) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668458761</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668458785</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668458792</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Managing Inflation and Supply Chain Disruptions in the Global Economy</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Ulas Akkucuk</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / International / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Inflation</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Logistics &amp; Supply Chain</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Inflation (Finance)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Industrial management--Effect of inflation on</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Business logistics</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>As the COVID-19 pandemic comes to a close, inflation has revealed itself to be a major problem for all countries of the developed world. The problem has been exacerbated in developing nations, which had problems even before the pandemic. Energy prices have increased, and with the increase in transportation costs, it has been more difficult for many retailers to stock shelves as they did before the pandemic. It is understood by many that the rising prices and supply chain disruptions will likely not be temporary and must be managed by future executives. Managing Inflation and Supply Chain Disruptions in the Global Economy uncovers the many ways businesses can manage this new phenomenon. It discusses global crises and their effects on the global economy in terms of inflation and supply chain. Covering topics such as inflationist impact, crisis leadership, and deglobalization, this premier reference source is an essential resource for economists, supply chain specialists, government officials, consultants, business leaders and executives, logistics professionals, IT managers, students and educators of higher education, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3366045&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="11">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3414015">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Nanochemistry : From Theory to Application for In-Depth Understanding of Nanomaterials</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Xuan Wang</au>
            <au>Sajid Bashir</au>
            <au>Jingbo Liu</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>De Gruyter STEM</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110739855</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110739879</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110739992</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Nanochemistry : From Theory to Application for In-Depth Understanding of Nanomaterials</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Xuan Wang</au>
            <au>Sajid Bashir</au>
            <au>Jingbo Liu</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Inorganic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Nanoscience</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Nanotechnology &amp; MEMS</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / Electronic Materials</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / Metals &amp; Alloys</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / Thin Films, Surfaces &amp; Interfaces</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Nanostructured materials</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Nanochemistry</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The modernization of science and technology using nanomaterials will open a new paradigm to meet the increasing energy demand. This book provides an in-depth understanding of theoretical perspectives from molecular and atomic levels. The modern analytical techniques explored provide an understanding of the interactions of particles at interfaces. This book gives a holistic view of materials synthesis, analysis, application, and safe handling.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3414015&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="12">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3387805">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Language and Emotion. Volume 1</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Gesine Lenore Schiewer</au>
            <au>Jeanette Altarriba</au>
            <au>Bee Chin Ng</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Language and Emotion</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110347487</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110347524</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110394603</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2023" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00001</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter Mouton</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Language and Emotion. Volume 1</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Gesine Lenore Schiewer</au>
            <au>Jeanette Altarriba</au>
            <au>Bee Chin Ng</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Language and emotions</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The Handbook consists of four major sections. Each section is introduced by a main article: Theories of Emotion – General Aspects Perspectives in Communication Theory, Semiotics, and Linguistics Perspectives on Language and Emotion in Cultural Studies Interdisciplinary and Applied Perspectives The first section presents interdisciplinary emotion theories relevant for the field of language and communication research, including the history of emotion research. The second section focuses on the full range of emotion-related aspects in linguistics, semiotics, and communication theories. The next section focuses on cultural studies and language and emotion; emotions in arts and literature, as well as research on emotion in literary studies; and media and emotion. The final section covers different domains, social practices, and applications, such as society, policy, diplomacy, economics and business communication, religion and emotional language, the domain of affective computing in human-machine interaction, and language and emotion research for language education. Overall, this Handbook represents a comprehensive overview in a rich, diverse compendium never before published in this particular domain.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3387805&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="13">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3406775">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Boston Children's Illustrated Tips and Tricks in Pediatric Orthopaedic Reconstructive Surgery</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Peter M Waters</au>
            <au>Benjamin J. Shore</au>
            <au>Daniel J. Hedequist</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781975103880</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781975103897</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Wolters Kluwer Health</pub>
          <place>Philadelphia</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Boston Children's Illustrated Tips and Tricks in Pediatric Orthopaedic Reconstructive Surgery</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Peter M Waters</au>
            <au>Benjamin J. Shore</au>
            <au>Daniel J. Hedequist</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Orthopedics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Pediatrics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Surgery / Orthopedic</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Infants</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Pediatric orthopedics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Children</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Originating from the esteemed Boston Children's Hospital, this new volume in the Illustrated Tips and Tricks series provides succinct, precise information from a wide range of experts on tackling technical problems in pediatric orthopaedic reconstructive surgery. Edited by Drs. Peter M. Waters, Benjamin J. Shore, and Daniel J. Hedequist, this volume presents practical, hands-on content gained from years of surgical experience, including nuggets of wisdom unique to particular institutions. Drawings, operative photos, and videos are used liberally throughout the book to illustrate surgical techniques and provide a handy visual complement to the text.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3406775&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="14">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3406779">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Operative Techniques in Joint Reconstruction Surgery</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Edwin Su</au>
            <au>Seth Jerabek</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781975172046</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781975174026</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <ed>3rd edition</ed>
          <pub>Wolters Kluwer Health</pub>
          <place>Philadelphia, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Operative Techniques in Joint Reconstruction Surgery</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Edwin Su</au>
            <au>Seth Jerabek</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Orthopedics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Sports Medicine</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Surgery / Orthopedic</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Knee--Surgery</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Hip joint--Surgery</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Arthroplasty</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Joints--Surgery</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Artificial joints</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Derived from Sam W. Wiesel and Todd J. Albert's four-volume Operative Techniques in Orthopaedic Surgery, this single-volume resource contains a comprehensive, authoritative review of a full range of joint reconstruction surgical procedures. In one convenient place, you'll find the entire Adult Reconstruction section, as well as relevant chapters from the Trauma section of Operative Techniques in Orthopaedic Surgery. Superb full-color illustrations and step-by-step explanations help you master surgical techniques, select the best procedure, avoid complications, and anticipate outcomes. Written by global experts from leading institutions, Operative Techniques in Joint Reconstruction Surgery, Third Edition, clearly demonstrates how to perform the techniques, making this an essential daily resource for residents, fellows, and practitioners.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3406779&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="15">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3406777">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Vitreous Microsurgery</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Steve Charles</au>
            <au>Stephen Huddleston</au>
            <au>Byron Wood</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781975168353</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781975168377</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <ed>6th edition</ed>
          <pub>Wolters Kluwer Health</pub>
          <place>Philadelphia, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Vitreous Microsurgery</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Steve Charles</au>
            <au>Stephen Huddleston</au>
            <au>Byron Wood</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Ophthalmology</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Microsurgery</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Vitreous body--Surgery</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Written by a world-renowned pioneer in vitreoretinal surgery, Vitreous Microsurgery, 6th Edition, is an up-to-date, comprehensive how-to guide to all vitreoretinal procedures. Dr. Steve Charles, along with Drs. Stephen Huddleston and Jonathan Brugger, takes readers step by step through the decision-making process for evaluating the best course of treatment, and describes in detail clinically proven methods of managing the anterior and posterior segment vitreous surgery patient in a systematic manner. Numerous algorithms assist with intraoperative decision making, relying on knowledge of physical principles and performed in the order of ascending risk.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3406777&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="16">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3387829">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Gasoline Additives</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Vahid Pirouzfar</au>
            <au>Mastane Narimani</au>
            <au>Ahmad Fayyaz Bakhsh</au>
            <au>Chia-Hung Su</au>
            <au>Milad Gharebaghi</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>De Gruyter Textbook</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110999952</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110989830</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110999969</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>[S.l.]</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Gasoline Additives</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Vahid Pirouzfar</au>
            <au>Mastane Narimani</au>
            <au>Ahmad Fayyaz Bakhsh</au>
            <au>Chia-Hung Su</au>
            <au>Milad Gharebaghi</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Petroleum</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Organic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Chemical &amp; Biochemical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Industrial Technology</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Motor fuels--Additives</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Gasoline--Additives</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Gasoline – the most common petroleum product comes in several types or grades. Straight-run gasoline is generated solely by crude oil distillation. Crack gasoline, derived by thermal or catalytic breaking of heavier oil fractions, accounts for the majority of gasoline used in automobile and aviation. Straight-run gasoline, fractured gasoline, reformed and synthetic gasoline, and additives are used to create a wide range of gasoline kinds.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3387829&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="17">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3387811">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Sepsis : Pathophysiologie, Diagnose und klinisches Management</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Markus Weigand</au>
            <au>Maximilian Dietrich</au>
            <au>Mathias Pletz</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Sepsis</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110673364</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110673395</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110673425</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Sepsis : Pathophysiologie, Diagnose und klinisches Management</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Markus Weigand</au>
            <au>Maximilian Dietrich</au>
            <au>Mathias Pletz</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Internal Medicine</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Clinical Medicine</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Emergency Medicine</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Septicemia--Treatment</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Septicemia--Diagnosis</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Septicemia</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Mit mehreren Millionen Todesfällen pro Jahr stellt die Sepsis eine der weltweit führenden Todesursachen dar und ist damit eine der größten Herausforderungen der Medizin. Trotz großer Fortschritte in der modernen Intensivmedizin ist die Sterblichkeit weiterhin hoch. Durch die frühzeitige Erkennung und Einleitung der Therapie können viele Todesfälle vermieden werden. Das Buch bietet eine prägnante und praxisorientierte Darstellung des aktuellen Wissensstandes für alle an der Behandlung der Sepsis beteiligten Ärztinnen und Ärzte sowie interessierte Personen aller Professionen.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="ger">German</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3387811&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="18">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3380370">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Innovation for Value and Mission : An Introduction to Innovation Management and Policy</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Peet van Biljon</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9783110711035</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110711066</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110711080</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Innovation for Value and Mission : An Introduction to Innovation Management and Policy</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Peet van Biljon</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / Business Development</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Entrepreneurship</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Leadership</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Public Affairs &amp; Administration</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / American Government / Local</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Organizational change</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Industrial management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Strategic planning</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Innovation. No other concept is so widely celebrated, yet so secretly dreaded. The reason: innovation requires managing through uncertainty. This is hard for any organization whether private or public, small or large. This book provides a roadmap for those who want to understand and manage innovation in all its aspects. It explains both the'how'and the'why'of innovation – its economic and policy context as well as the techniques by which it can be orchestrated, along with the management systems needed to govern it. Innovation is uniquely presented through both a private-sector (value-creating) and public-sector (mission-fulfilling) lens. Topics covered in context include modern innovation and creativity techniques such as design thinking and the Lean Startup, the organizational challenges of innovation, as well as innovation project- and portfolio management techniques. Business-model innovation and open innovation complete the picture from the manager's perspective. The private and public financing of R&amp;D, startups, and corporate innovation are presented – contrasting the private and public worlds while explaining how they complement each other. Government innovation policy is discussed in its historical and contemporary context, and the innovation policy toolset is introduced. Continual innovation is vital for companies and countries to prosper. Readers will learn why innovation must follow technological breakthroughs to raise productivity and economic growth, and how innovation – when done right – can benefit larger society. An explanation for unequal growth – that some companies, regions, and countries are not seeing the full productivity gains promised by modern technology – is explored in the context of technology diffusion. No previous experience in innovation management, economics or public policy is assumed, and the book moves fast to equip the reader with practical tools and techniques. Innovation for Value and Mission is suitable for an introductory graduate level course, or as a desk reference for experienced practitioners and policymakers. Because it connects multiple topic areas and contains ample additional references, the book is also a great resource for those with expertise in one particular area of innovation who desire to branch out into other areas.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3380370&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="19">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3377021">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Multidisciplinary Perspectives Towards Building a Digitally Competent Society</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Sanjeev Bansal</au>
            <au>Vandana Ahuja</au>
            <au>Vijit Chaturvedi</au>
            <au>Vinamra Jain</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Human and Social Aspects of Technology (AHSAT) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668452745</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668452769</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668452776</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Multidisciplinary Perspectives Towards Building a Digitally Competent Society</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Sanjeev Bansal</au>
            <au>Vandana Ahuja</au>
            <au>Vijit Chaturvedi</au>
            <au>Vinamra Jain</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Social Aspects</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Social Aspects</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Human-Computer Interaction (HCI)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Information technology--Social aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Organizational change</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The world is undergoing a transformation as technology enters every ecosystem. Subsequently, there is a need to develop higher-order digital skills to ensure one's employability as professionals need to build digital competencies to remain competitive in the current work environment. Additionally, businesses must also continue to update their digital practices in order to remain relevant. Multidisciplinary Perspectives Towards Building a Digitally Competent Society explores multidisciplinary perspectives towards building a more digitally competent society, considers new business models and the need for organizations and individuals to develop the right mindset to embrace digitalization, and discusses how social capital can become a key driver in crafting a whole new digitally competent social fabric. Covering topics such as technological transformation, social media, and corporate social responsibility, this reference work is ideal for corporate practitioners, business owners, policymakers, scholars, researchers, practitioners, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3377021&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="20">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3377012">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Unmanned Aerial Vehicles and Multidisciplinary Applications Using AI Techniques</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Bella Mary I. Thusnavis</au>
            <au>K. Martin Sagayam</au>
            <au>Ahmed A. Elngar</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Computational Intelligence and Robotics (ACIR) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799887638</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799887652</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799887669</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Unmanned Aerial Vehicles and Multidisciplinary Applications Using AI Techniques</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Bella Mary I. Thusnavis</au>
            <au>K. Martin Sagayam</au>
            <au>Ahmed A. Elngar</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Artificial Intelligence / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Agriculture / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Robotics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Drone aircraft--Industrial applications</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Aerial surveillance</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs) and artificial intelligence (AI) are gaining the attention of academic and industrial researchers due to the freedoms that UAVs afford when operating and monitoring activities remotely. Applying machine learning and deep learning techniques can result in fast and reliable outputs and have helped in real-time monitoring, data collection and processing, and prediction. UAVs utilizing these techniques can become instrumental tools for computer/wireless networks, smart cities, military applications, agricultural sectors, and mining. Unmanned Aerial Vehicles and Multidisciplinary Applications Using AI Techniques is an essential reference source that covers pattern recognition, machine and deep learning-based methods, and other AI techniques and the impact they have when applied to different real-time applications of UAVs. It synthesizes the scope and importance of machine learning and deep learning models in enhancing UAV capabilities, solutions to problems, and numerous application areas. Covering topics such as vehicular surveillance systems, yield prediction, and human activity recognition, this premier reference source is a comprehensive resource for computer scientists; AI engineers; data scientists; agriculturalists; government officials; military leaders; business managers and leaders; students and faculty of higher education; academic libraries; academicians; and researchers in computer science, computer vision, pattern recognition, imaging, and engineering.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3377012&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="21">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3377013">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Reciprocity and Its Practice in Social Research</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Jahid Siraz Chowdhury</au>
            <au>Haris Abd Wahab</au>
            <au>Rashid Mohd Saad</au>
            <au>Hasan Reza</au>
            <au>Mokbul Morshed Ahmad</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Religious and Cultural Studies (ARCS) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799896029</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896043</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896050</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Reciprocity and Its Practice in Social Research</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Jahid Siraz Chowdhury</au>
            <au>Haris Abd Wahab</au>
            <au>Rashid Mohd Saad</au>
            <au>Hasan Reza</au>
            <au>Mokbul Morshed Ahmad</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / Social</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Research</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Social sciences--Research--Methodology</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Reciprocity (Psychology)--Social aspects</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Reciprocity has been critical in the philosophy and social sciences of the 20th century. Over the last seven decades, several countries settled by European powers have become autonomous, and returning has become a challenge. Consequently, writing on reciprocity as a central theme requires time and implies a deep dedication to the community. There is a need to explore the factors and policies behind the study agendas and secret philosophies before and after European involvement. Reciprocity and Its Practice in Social Research aims to open the controlled consciousness of self as a human being and then as a scholar to the community via the methodological lens. It analyzes reciprocity from the Greek tradition to Medeabale Arab to the early colonial or pre-colonial period. It specifically addresses the benefit of social research on the community and seeks ways to revolutionize and improve current research and academic processes. Covering topics such as the philosophy of science, indigenous science, and Western metaphysics, this book is an essential resource for anthropologists, philosophers, sociologists, university faculty and administration, students of higher education, librarians, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3377013&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="22">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3366047">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Post-Pandemic Talent Management Models in Knowledge Organizations</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Mohammad Rafiqul Islam Talukdar</au>
            <au>Carmen Z. Lamagna</au>
            <au>Charles Carillo Villanueva</au>
            <au>Rezbin Nahar</au>
            <au>Farheen Hassan</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Logistics, Operations, and Management Science (ALOMS) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668438947</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668438961</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668438978</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Post-Pandemic Talent Management Models in Knowledge Organizations</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Mohammad Rafiqul Islam Talukdar</au>
            <au>Carmen Z. Lamagna</au>
            <au>Charles Carillo Villanueva</au>
            <au>Rezbin Nahar</au>
            <au>Farheen Hassan</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Leadership</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Human Resources &amp; Personnel Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Personnel management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Human capital--Management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Manpower planning</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>In today's modern business world, the dominant factor of any organization's success is human capital. Appropriately acquiring and managing talented staff is crucial to the growth and development of companies and provides them with a considerable competitive advantage in the industry. Further study on the importance of talent management is required to ensure businesses are able to thrive in the present environment. Post-Pandemic Talent Management Models in Knowledge Organizations discusses strategic human resource management and the talent management of post-modern knowledge-based organizations during the COVID-19 pandemic and post-pandemic paradigm. Covering critical topics such as organizational performance and creative work behavior, this major reference work is ideal for managers, business owners, entrepreneurs, academicians, researchers, scholars, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3366047&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="23">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3360144">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>The Minimal Intervention</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Lucius Burckhardt</au>
            <au>Markus Ritter</au>
            <au>Martin Schmitz</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9783035625301</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783035625318</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Birkhäuser</pub>
          <place>Basel</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>The Minimal Intervention</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Lucius Burckhardt</au>
            <au>Markus Ritter</au>
            <au>Martin Schmitz</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">ARCHITECTURE / Urban &amp; Land Use Planning</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Design--Philosophy</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">City planning--Environmental aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Urban ecology (Sociology)</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Die Sichtweise als Designprinzip Lucius Burckhardt (1925–2003) schrieb seine Theorie Der kleinstmögliche Eingriff bereits Anfang der 1980er-Jahre. Die Idee des minimalen Eingriffs zieht sich durch sein gesamtes Werk, von der Kritik des Urbanismus bis zur Wissenschaft des Gehens. Der „kleinstmögliche Eingriff“ steht für eine Planungstheorie, die auf der Ebene der Landschaftsgestaltung davon ausgeht, dass es zwei „Landschaften“ gibt: die tatsächlich sichtbare und die in unseren Köpfen. Die Theorie des kleinsten Eingriffs bedeutet, nicht mit gewaltigen Mitteln in die bestehende Landschaft einzugreifen, sondern auf das Landschaftsbild in unseren Köpfen einzuwirken und ein ästhetisches Verständnis der Umwelt zu schaffen. Der Schweizer Soziologe wendet in diesem erstmals auf Englisch erhältlichen Buch die Formel auf viele Gestaltungsbereiche an. Gedankliches Konzentrat von Lucius Burckhardts Theorien erstmals auf Englisch Zusammenhänge der Planung und des Bauwesens Rationalisierung und Bedürfnisse</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3360144&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="24">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3360140">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Modern Environmental Design : A Project Primer for Complex Forms</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Andrew Watts</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9783035621433</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783035621471</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Birkhäuser</pub>
          <place>Basel</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Modern Environmental Design : A Project Primer for Complex Forms</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Andrew Watts</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">ARCHITECTURE / Methods &amp; Materials</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">ARCHITECTURE / Professional Practice</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">ARCHITECTURE / Sustainability &amp; Green Design</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Sustainable buildings--Design and construction</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Architecture and society--Environmental aspects</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Well-being in a building depends on a number of factors. Visuals, ventilation, heat, cooling, and acoustics are all key. Its efficiency relates not only to the design of a building; it can also be optimized and automated using the latest technologies and innovative environmentally friendly low-tech solutions. To build upon and add to the successful Modern Construction Handbook, Andrew Watts details innovative and established examples of interior design in Modern Environmental Design. These are presented with the aid of texts, drawings and 3D renderings.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3360140&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="25">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3341351">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Hands-On Data Structures and Algorithms with Python : Store, Manipulate, and Access Data Effectively and Boost the Performance of Your Applications</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Dr. Basant Agarwal</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781801073448</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781801076814</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <ed>Third edition</ed>
          <pub>Packt Publishing</pub>
          <place>Birmingham, UK</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Hands-On Data Structures and Algorithms with Python : Store, Manipulate, and Access Data Effectively and Boost the Performance of Your Applications</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Dr. Basant Agarwal</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Languages / Python</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Python (Computer program language)</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Understand how implementing different data structures and algorithms intelligently can make your Python code and applications more maintainable and efficientKey FeaturesExplore functional and reactive implementations of traditional and advanced data structuresApply a diverse range of algorithms in your Python codeImplement the skills you have learned to maximize the performance of your applicationsBook DescriptionChoosing the right data structure is pivotal to optimizing the performance and scalability of applications. This new edition of Hands-On Data Structures and Algorithms with Python will expand your understanding of key structures, including stacks, queues, and lists, and also show you how to apply priority queues and heaps in applications. You'll learn how to analyze and compare Python algorithms, and understand which algorithms should be used for a problem based on running time and computational complexity. You will also become confident organizing your code in a manageable, consistent, and scalable way, which will boost your productivity as a Python developer. By the end of this Python book, you'll be able to manipulate the most important data structures and algorithms to more efficiently store, organize, and access data in your applications.What you will learnUnderstand common data structures and algorithms using examples, diagrams, and exercisesExplore how more complex structures, such as priority queues and heaps, can benefit your codeImplement searching, sorting, and selection algorithms on number and string sequencesBecome confident with key string-matching algorithmsUnderstand algorithmic paradigms and apply dynamic programming techniquesUse asymptotic notation to analyze algorithm performance with regard to time and space complexitiesWrite powerful, robust code using the latest features of PythonWho this book is forThis book is for developers and programmers who are interested in learning about data structures and algorithms in Python to write complex, flexible programs. Basic Python programming knowledge is expected.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3341351&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="26">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3331845">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Global Perspectives on International Advertising</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Ipek Krom</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Marketing, Customer Relationship Management, and E-services (AMCRMES) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799896722</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896746</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896753</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Global Perspectives on International Advertising</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Ipek Krom</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Advertising &amp; Promotion</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Marketing / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / International / Marketing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Advertising--Case studies</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Advertising--Cross-cultural studies</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>International advertising is an important discipline in social sciences studies and though many books and articles have been published surrounding international advertising, only a few of them contain information about the advertising industry related to specific international countries and regions. Additional consideration on how advertising is utilized across the world is vital to understand the current best practices, challenges, and opportunities in the marketing field. The Handbook of Research on Global Perspectives on International Advertising considers various perspectives on international advertising through global and local lenses and discusses strategies and tactics of advertising across the globe. Covering topics such as branding, political advertising, cultural features, and tourism advertising, this reference work is ideal for industry professionals, academicians, practitioners, researchers, scholars, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3331845&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="27">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3331834">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Digital Innovation and Networking in Post-COVID-19 Organizations</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Ana Pego</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Business Strategy and Competitive Advantage (ABSCA) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668467626</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668467633</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668467640</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Digital Innovation and Networking in Post-COVID-19 Organizations</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Ana Pego</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Networking / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Organizational Development</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Business networks--Management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Technological innovations</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">COVID-19 Pandemic, 2020---Influence</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Businesses have had to face many challenges due to the COVID-19 pandemic; to survive in the changing landscape, they had to adapt quickly and implement new tactics and best practices to stay competitive. Networking is one of the many areas that looks vastly different in a post-pandemic world and companies must understand this change or risk falling behind. Further study is required to uncover the various difficulties and potential future directions of networking and innovation within the business landscape. The Handbook of Research on Digital Innovation and Networking in Post-COVID-19 Organizations provides a thorough overview of the ways in which organizations have had to change and adapt to the new business environments and considers how networking looks different in a post-COVID-19 world. Covering key topics such as organizational structures, consumer behavior, teleworking, and collaborations, this major reference work is ideal for managers, business owners, industry professionals, policymakers, researchers, scholars, academicians, practitioners, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3331834&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="28">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3331828">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Critical Perspectives on Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion in Marketing</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Ayantunji Gbadamosi</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781668435908</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668435922</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668435939</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Critical Perspectives on Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion in Marketing</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Ayantunji Gbadamosi</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Sales &amp; Selling / Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Consumer Behavior</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Minority Studies</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Business ethics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Marketing--Moral and ethical aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Young consumers</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Marketers have attracted criticism from advocates of marketing ethics for not giving equal attention to all consumers. In other contexts, other nomenclatures such as “less privileged” or “low-income consumers” are being used to describe consumers. However, a critical view of the scope of the disadvantaged consumers shows that it is beyond having limited income and encapsulates all forms of limitations that prevent full inclusion in marketplace opportunities. Critical Perspectives on Diversity, Equity, and inclusion in Marketing focuses on exploring diversity, equity, and inclusion in marketing as related to individuals, groups, organizations, and societies. It provides insight into consumption practices, diversity, inclusion, limitations, and their theoretical and practical implications. Covering topics such as ethnic identity negotiation, marketing implications, and consumer vulnerability, this premier reference source is an eclectic resource for business leaders and managers, marketers, sociologists, DEI professionals, libraries, students and educators of higher education, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3331828&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="29">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3331831">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Interdisciplinary Reflections of Contemporary Experiential Marketing Practices</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Gökhan Akel</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Marketing, Customer Relationship Management, and E-services (AMCRMES) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668443804</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668443828</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668443835</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Interdisciplinary Reflections of Contemporary Experiential Marketing Practices</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Gökhan Akel</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Marketing / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Sales &amp; Selling / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / E-Commerce / Digital Marketing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Tourism</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Marketing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Management</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Technology has brought many innovations and changes in experiential design and experiential products and services. The digital transformations brought about by technology have led to problem-solving, creative functioning, and unique improvements along with experiences. Human-digital experience interaction prevails in many areas of modern society, and in order to evaluate this interaction, a more balanced understanding of digital and experience processes is required. The Handbook of Research on Interdisciplinary Reflections of Contemporary Experiential Marketing Practices discusses innovative research on experiential marketing and evaluates the interdisciplinary reflections of practices from different perspectives. The book also explores how the concept of experience is developed, managed, and marketed according to current consumer needs and motivations. Covering critical topics such as experience economy and tourism experience management, this reference work is ideal for managers, marketers, hospitality professionals, academicians, practitioners, scholars, researchers, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3331831&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="30">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3331833">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Artificial Intelligence Applications in Agriculture and Food Quality Improvement</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Mohammad Ayoub Khan</au>
            <au>Rijwan Khan</au>
            <au>Pushkar Praveen</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Computational Intelligence and Robotics (ACIR) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668451410</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668451434</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668451441</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Artificial Intelligence Applications in Agriculture and Food Quality Improvement</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Mohammad Ayoub Khan</au>
            <au>Rijwan Khan</au>
            <au>Pushkar Praveen</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Agriculture / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Artificial Intelligence / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Food Science / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Artificial intelligence</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Agriculture--Data processing</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Food is a necessary aspect of human life, and agriculture is crucial to any country's global economy. Because the food business is essential to both a country's economy and global economy, artificial intelligence (AI)-based smart solutions are needed to assure product quality and food safety. The agricultural sector is constantly under pressure to boost crop output as a result of population growth. This necessitates the use of AI applications. Artificial Intelligence Applications in Agriculture and Food Quality Improvement discusses the application of AI, machine learning, and data analytics for the acceleration of the agricultural and food sectors. It presents a comprehensive view of how these technologies and tools are used for agricultural process improvement, food safety, and food quality improvement. Covering topics such as diet assessment research, crop yield prediction, and precision farming, this premier reference source is an essential resource for food safety professionals, quality assurance professionals, agriculture specialists, crop managers, agricultural engineers, food scientists, computer scientists, AI specialists, students, libraries, government officials, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3331833&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="31">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3331827">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Leadership Strategies for the Hybrid Workforce : Best Practices for Fostering Employee Safety and Significance</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Matthew Ohlson</au>
            <au>Lakshmi Goel</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Human Resources Management and Organizational Development (AHRMOD) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668434536</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668434550</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668434567</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Leadership Strategies for the Hybrid Workforce : Best Practices for Fostering Employee Safety and Significance</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Matthew Ohlson</au>
            <au>Lakshmi Goel</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Organizational Behavior</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Leadership</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">LAW / Labor &amp; Employment</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Organizational change--Management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Virtual reality in management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Telecommuting--Management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Leadership</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Virtual work teams--Management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Employee morale</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Organizational change</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The global shift of the business world and the way the workforce navigates jobs is a powerful consequence of the global pandemic. Moreover, occupational health and safety initiatives are at the forefront of managerial discussions. Workplace trends show that the flexibility and adaptability demonstrated during the COVID-19 pandemic may prove to offer organizations new insights into employee recruitment, retention, and production. Leadership Strategies for the Hybrid Workforce: Best Practices for Fostering Employee Safety and Significance shares the strategies and best practices in making employees feel valued and significant—a key factor in both employee recruitment and retention and one that goes far beyond mere pay increases. It uses lessons learned from the COVID-19 pandemic to discuss these new organizational strategies. Covering topics such as digital change, employee significance, and organizational DNA, this book is an essential resource for business leaders, students and educators of higher education, human resource managers, CEOs, managers, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3331827&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="32">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3331829">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Aspects and Applications of Incompressible and Compressible Aerodynamics</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Sathish K. Kumar</au>
            <au>Naren Shankar Radhakrishnan</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Mechatronics and Mechanical Engineering (AMME) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668442302</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668442326</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668442333</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Aspects and Applications of Incompressible and Compressible Aerodynamics</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Sathish K. Kumar</au>
            <au>Naren Shankar Radhakrishnan</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Mechanics / Aerodynamics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Aeronautics &amp; Astronautics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Mechanical</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Compressibility</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Aerodynamics</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Aerodynamics is a science that improves the ability to understand theoretical basics and apply fundamental physics in real-life problems. The study of the motion of air, both externally over an airplane wing and internally over a scramjet engine intake, has acknowledged the significance of studying both incompressible and compressible flow aerodynamics. The Handbook of Research on Aspects and Applications of Incompressible and Compressible Aerodynamics discusses all aspects of aerodynamics from application to theory. It further presents the equations and mathematical models used to describe and characterize flow fields as well as their thermodynamic aspects and applications. Covering topics such as airplane configurations, hypersonic vehicles, and the parametric effect of roughness, this premier reference source is an essential resource for engineers, scientists, students and educators of higher education, military experts, libraries, government officials, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3331829&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="33">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3307115">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>European Cities : Modernity, Race and Colonialism</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Noa K. Ha</au>
            <au>Giovanni Picker</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781526158437</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781526158420</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781526158444</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Manchester University Press</pub>
          <place>Manchester</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>European Cities : Modernity, Race and Colonialism</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Noa K. Ha</au>
            <au>Giovanni Picker</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Sociology / Urban</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">HISTORY / Europe / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Human Geography</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Cultural pluralism--Europe</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Postcolonialism--Europe</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Cities and towns--Europe</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Sociology, Urban--Europe</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Minorities--Europe--Social conditions</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>European cities: Modernity, race and colonialism is a multidisciplinary collection of scholarly studies which rethink European urban modernity from a race-conscious perspective, being aware of (post-)colonial entanglements. The twelve original contributions empirically focus on such various cities as Barcelona, Buenos Aires, Cottbus, Genoa, Hamburg, Madrid, Mitrovica, Naples, Paris, Sheffield, and Thessaloniki, engaging multiple combinations of global urban studies, from various historical perspectives, with postcolonial, decolonial and critical race studies. Primarily inspired by the notion of Provincializing Europe (Dipesh Chakrabarty) the collection interrogates dominant, Eurocentric theories, representations and models of European cities across the East-West divide, offering the reader alternative perspectives to understand and imagine urban life and politics. With its focus on Europe, this book ultimately contributes to decades of rigorous critical race scholarship on varied global urban regions.European cities is a vital reading for anyone interested in the complex interactions between colonial legacies and constructions of'modernity', in view of catering to social change and urban justice.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3307115&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="34">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3301759">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Building Inclusive Global Knowledge Societies for Sustainable Development</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Cristina Raluca Gh. Popescu</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Practice, Progress, and Proficiency in Sustainability (PPPS) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668451090</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668451106</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668451113</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Building Inclusive Global Knowledge Societies for Sustainable Development</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Cristina Raluca Gh. Popescu</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / Sustainable Development</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Knowledge Capital</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Information society</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Sustainable development</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Knowledge and information have significant impacts on individuals'daily lives and activities, especially when referring to the new economy and the global knowledge societies. However, the COVID-19 pandemic has caused massive disruptions in the creation of the vital inclusive global information society. Due to this change, further study on the current difficulties and best practices of creating global knowledge societies is required in order to ensure communities can continue to advance and information is shared appropriately. The Handbook of Research on Building Inclusive Global Knowledge Societies for Sustainable Development aims at providing an updated view of the newest trends, novel practices, and latest tendencies concerning building inclusive global knowledge societies for sustainable development while focusing on the benefits and the opportunities derived from the new economy and the global knowledge societies. Covering topics such as smart cities, food security, and climate change, this major reference work is ideal for policymakers, government officials, business owners, managers, academicians, scholars, researchers, practitioners, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3301759&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="35">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3301763">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Developing Competencies for Pre-Health Professional Students, Advisors, and Programs</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Rohini Ganjoo</au>
            <au>Lisa S. Schwartz</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781668459690</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668459706</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668459713</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Medical Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, Pennsylvania [701 E. Chocolate Avenue, Hershey, Pennsylvania, 17033, USA]</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Developing Competencies for Pre-Health Professional Students, Advisors, and Programs</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Rohini Ganjoo</au>
            <au>Lisa S. Schwartz</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Education &amp; Training</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">EDUCATION / Schools / Levels / Higher</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">EDUCATION / Teacher &amp; Student Mentoring</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Clinical competence</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Premedical education</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Medical education</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Today, there is a significant need for healthcare professionals across disciplines and sectors as the world faces unprecedented health challenges and adopts innovative healthcare technologies. Despite this demand for a competent and eager healthcare workforce, the education and processes to becoming a qualified healthcare professional are complex and intricate, which may turn people away from this path due to confusion, fear, or doubt. In order to encourage and support those involved in medical education, further study on the best practices and challenges of developing confident and capable health professionals is required. The Handbook of Research on Developing Competencies for Pre-Health Professional Students, Advisors, and Programs provides insight into the critical skills and expertise essential for those interested in pursuing employment in healthcare as well as current procedures and training to support them during their academic and professional careers. Covering topics such as lifelong learning skills, healthcare professions, and strategic learning, this major reference work is crucial for advisors, nurses, healthcare professionals, academicians, researchers, practitioners, scholars, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3301763&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="36">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3301760">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Research Anthology on Social Media Advertising and Building Consumer Relationships</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Information Resources Management Association</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781668462874</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668462881</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668462898</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Research Anthology on Social Media Advertising and Building Consumer Relationships</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Information Resources Management Association</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Internet / Social Media</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Advertising &amp; Promotion</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Customer Relations</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Internet marketing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Internet advertising</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Social media--Economic aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Customer relations</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Social media has become a key tool that businesses must utilize in all areas of their practices to build relationships with their customer base and promote their products. This technology is no longer optional as those who do not take advantage of the many benefits it offers continue to struggle with outdated practices. In order for businesses to flourish, further study on the advantages social media provides in the areas of marketing and developing consumer relationships is required. The Research Anthology on Social Media Advertising and Building Consumer Relationships considers best practices and strategies of utilizing social media successfully throughout various business fields to promote products, build relationships, and maintain relevancy. This book also discusses common pitfalls and challenges companies face as they attempt to create a name for themselves in the online world. Covering topics such as marketing, human aspects of business, and branding, this major reference work is crucial for managers, business owners, entrepreneurs, researchers, scholars, academicians, practitioners, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3301760&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="37">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3300803">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>The Tragic Science : How Economists Cause Harm (Even As They Aspire to Do Good)</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>George F. DeMartino</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9780226821238</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9780226821245</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>University of Chicago Press</pub>
          <place>Chicago</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>The Tragic Science : How Economists Cause Harm (Even As They Aspire to Do Good)</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>George F. DeMartino</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Business Ethics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Economics / Comparative</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Economics / Theory</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Economics--Moral and ethical aspects</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>A forceful critique of the social science that has ruled—and damaged—the modern world. The practice of economics, as economists will tell you, is a powerful force for good. Economists are the guardians of the world's economies and financial systems. The applications of economic theory can alleviate poverty, reduce disease, and promote sustainability. While this narrative has been successfully propagated by economists, it belies a more challenging truth: economic interventions, including those economists deem successful, also cause harm. Sometimes the harm is manageable and short-lived. But just as often the harm is deep, enduring, and even irreparable. And too often the harm falls on those least able to survive it. In The Tragic Science, George F. DeMartino says what economists have too long repressed: that economists do great harm even as they aspire to do good. Economist-induced harm, DeMartino shows, results in part from economists'“irreparable ignorance”—from the fact that they know far less than they tend to believe they know—and from disciplinary training that treats the human tolls of economic policies and interventions as simply the costs of promoting social betterment. DeMartino details the complicated nature of economic harm, explores economists'frequent failure to recognize it, and makes a sobering case for professional humility and for genuine respect for those who stand to be harmed by economists'practice. At a moment in history when the economics profession holds enormous power, DeMartino's work demonstrates the downside of its influence and the responsibility facing those who practice the tragic science.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3300803&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="38">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3300391">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Dating the Old Norse Poetic Edda : A Multifactorial Analysis of Linguistic Features</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Christopher D. Sapp</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Studies in Germanic Linguistics</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9789027211156</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9789027257710</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00005</vid>
          <pub>John Benjamins Publishing Company</pub>
          <place>Amsterdam</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Dating the Old Norse Poetic Edda : A Multifactorial Analysis of Linguistic Features</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Christopher D. Sapp</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / Historical &amp; Comparative</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Manuscript dating</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Eddas--History and criticism</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Old Norse poetry--History and criticism</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Manuscripts, Old Norse</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This book offers new dating of the poems of the Old Norse Poetic Edda, perhaps our best sources about the mythology and legends of the Viking Age. This study compares the anonymous Eddic poems to dated skaldic poems with respect to five phenomena that develop diachronically in early Old Norse: the expletive particle of, types of negation, word order, types of relative clause, and metrical criteria. After examining these dating features individually, the three most reliable criteria—the particle of, negation, and relative clause type—are combined into a multifactorial analysis using a Naïve Bayes Classifier. The classifier assigns a date to each Eddic poem, and these proposed dates have interesting implications for our understanding of these texts as sources for the medieval history, mythology, linguistics, and literature of the Germanic peoples. This book will have broad interdisciplinary interest, not just to historical linguists and philologists but also to scholars of Norse history, literature, and mythology.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3300391&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="39">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3297126">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Happiness in Action : A Philosopher’s Guide to the Good Life</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Adam Adatto Sandel</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9780674268647</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9780674287327</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9780674287310</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Harvard University Press</pub>
          <place>Cambridge, Massachusetts</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Happiness in Action : A Philosopher’s Guide to the Good Life</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Adam Adatto Sandel</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / Ethics &amp; Moral Philosophy</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / Mind &amp; Body</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / Political</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / Social</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Public Policy / Social Policy</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SELF-HELP / Personal Growth / Happiness</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Self-actualization (Psychology)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Self-realization--Philosophy</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Well-being--Philosophy</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>“Here, at last, is a book about what happiness really means, and why it often eludes us in our stressed-out, always-on lives.”—Arianna Huffington, Founder and CEO, ThriveA young philosopher and Guinness World Record holder in pull-ups argues that the key to happiness is not goal-driven striving but forging a life that integrates self-possession, friendship, and engagement with nature.What is the meaning of the good life? In this strikingly original book, Adam Adatto Sandel draws on ancient and modern thinkers and on two seemingly disparate pursuits of his own, philosophy and fitness, to offer a surprising answer to this age-old human question.Sandel argues that finding fulfillment is not about attaining happiness, conceived as a state of mind, or even about accomplishing one's greatest goals. Instead, true happiness comes from immersing oneself in activity that is intrinsically rewarding. The source of meaning, he suggests, derives from the integrity or “wholeness” of self that we forge throughout the journey of life.At the heart of Sandel's account of life as a journey are three virtues that get displaced and distorted by our goal-oriented striving: self-possession, friendship, and engagement with nature. Sandel offers illuminating and counterintuitive accounts of these virtues, revealing how they are essential to a happiness that lasts.To illustrate the struggle of living up to these virtues, Sandel looks to literature, film, and television, and also to his own commitments and adventures. A focal point of his personal narrative is a passion that, at first glance, is as narrow a goal-oriented pursuit as one can imagine: training to set the Guinness World Record for Most Pull-Ups in One Minute. Drawing on his own experiences, Sandel makes philosophy accessible for readers who, in their own infinitely various ways, struggle with the tension between goal-oriented striving and the embrace of life as a journey.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3297126&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="40">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3297125">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Getting to Diversity : What Works and What Doesn’t</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Frank Dobbin</au>
            <au>Alexandra Kalev</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9780674276611</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9780674290051</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Belknap Press</pub>
          <place>Cambridge</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Getting to Diversity : What Works and What Doesn’t</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Frank Dobbin</au>
            <au>Alexandra Kalev</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Organizational Behavior</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Economics / Theory</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Public Policy / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">PSYCHOLOGY / Industrial &amp; Organizational Psychology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Sociology / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Diversity in the workplace</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Organizational change</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Discrimination in employment</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>“Too many companies don't know how to walk the walk of diversity, equity, and inclusion. Getting to Diversity shows them how.”—Lori George Billingsley, former Global Chief DEI Officer, Coca-Cola CompanyIn an authoritative, data-driven account, two of the world's leading management experts challenge dominant approaches to increasing workplace diversity and provide a comprehensive account of what really works.Every year America becomes more diverse, but change in the makeup of the management ranks has stalled. The problem has become an urgent matter of national debate. How do we fix it? Bestselling books preach moral reformation. Employers, however well intentioned, follow guesswork and whatever their peers happen to be doing. Arguing that it's time to focus on changing systems rather than individuals, two of the world's leading experts on workplace diversity show us a better way in the first comprehensive, data-driven analysis of what succeeds and what fails. The surprising results will change how America works.Frank Dobbin and Alexandra Kalev draw on more than thirty years of data from eight hundred companies as well as in-depth interviews with managers. The research shows just how little companies gain from standard practice: sending managers to diversity training to reveal their biases, then following up with hiring and promotion rules, and sanctions, to shape their behavior. Almost nothing changes. It's time, Dobbin and Kalev argue, to focus on changing the management systems that make it hard for women and people of color to succeed. They show us how the best firms are pioneering new recruitment, mentoring, and skill training systems, and implementing strategies for mixing segregated work groups to increase diversity. They explain what a difference ambitious work–life programs make. And they argue that as firms adopt new systems, the key to making them work is to make them accessible to all—not just the favored few.Powerful, authoritative, and driven by a commitment to change, Getting to Diversity is the book we need now to address constructively one of the most fraught challenges in American life.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3297125&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="41">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3297129">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>The Triumph of Broken Promises : The End of the Cold War and the Rise of Neoliberalism</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Fritz Bartel</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9780674976788</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9780674275805</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Harvard University Press</pub>
          <place>Cambridge, Massachusetts</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>The Triumph of Broken Promises : The End of the Cold War and the Rise of Neoliberalism</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Fritz Bartel</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Economic History</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">HISTORY / Europe / Eastern</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">HISTORY / Russia &amp; the Former Soviet Union</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">HISTORY / United States / 20th Century</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / International Relations / Diplomacy</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Recessions--History--20th century</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Financial crises--History--20th century</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Neoliberalism</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Cold War</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Capitalism--History--20th century</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>A powerful case that the economic shocks of the 1970s hastened both the end of the Cold War and the rise of neoliberalism by forcing governments to impose austerity on their own people.Why did the Cold War come to a peaceful end? And why did neoliberal economics sweep across the world in the late twentieth century? In this pathbreaking study, Fritz Bartel argues that the answer to these questions is one and the same. The Cold War began as a competition between capitalist and communist governments to expand their social contracts as they raced to deliver their people a better life. But the economic shocks of the 1970s made promises of better living untenable on both sides of the Iron Curtain. Energy and financial markets placed immense pressure on governments to discipline their social contracts. Rather than make promises, political leaders were forced to break them.In a sweeping narrative, The Triumph of Broken Promises tells the story of how the pressure to break promises spurred the end of the Cold War. In the West, neoliberalism provided Western leaders like Ronald Reagan and Margaret Thatcher with the political and ideological tools to shut down industries, impose austerity, and favor the interests of capital over labor. But in Eastern Europe, revolutionaries like Lech Walesa in Poland resisted any attempt at imposing market discipline. Mikhail Gorbachev tried in vain to reform the Soviet system, but the necessary changes ultimately presented too great a challenge.Faced with imposing economic discipline antithetical to communist ideals, Soviet-style governments found their legitimacy irreparably damaged. But in the West, politicians could promote austerity as an antidote to the excesses of ideological opponents, setting the stage for the rise of the neoliberal global economy.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3297129&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="42">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3290804">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Green Chemistry : Water and Its Treatment</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Mark Anthony Benvenuto</au>
            <au>Heinz Plaumann</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Green Chemical Processing</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110597301</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110597820</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110598063</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00007</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Green Chemistry : Water and Its Treatment</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Mark Anthony Benvenuto</au>
            <au>Heinz Plaumann</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Environmental Science</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Industrial &amp; Technical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Chemical &amp; Biochemical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Environmental</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Water--Purification--Environmental aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Green chemistry</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The “greening” of industry processes, i.e. making them more sustainable, is a popular and often lucrative trend in Chemical Engineering. The 7th volume of Green Chemical Processing considers the role of water in sustainable chemistry and highlights innovations in the field of water treatment. The American Chemical Society's 12 Principles of Green Chemistry are woven throughout this text as well as the series to which this book belongs.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3290804&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="43">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3290812">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Rare Earth Elements : Analytics</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Alfred Golloch</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>De Gruyter Reference</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110696363</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110696455</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110696646</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <ed>2nd edition</ed>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Rare Earth Elements : Analytics</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Alfred Golloch</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Inorganic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Analytic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Physical &amp; Theoretical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Spectroscopy &amp; Spectrum Analysis</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Rare earths</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The reference work describes in its new edition still more up-to-date methods for the recycling and purifi cation processes of rare earth element analysis for industrial and scientific purposes alike. Due to their vast applications, from computer hardware to mobile phones and electric cars, REEs have become a valuable resource for our modern life. New topics: emission spectroscopy, analysis of environmental samples and pharmaceutical applications.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3290812&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="44">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3290806">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Advanced Concepts and Applications</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Fidele Ntie-Kang</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Chemoinformatics of Natural Products</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110668889</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110668896</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110669060</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00002</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Advanced Concepts and Applications</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Fidele Ntie-Kang</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Analytic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Clinical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Organic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Industrial &amp; Technical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Nanotechnology &amp; MEMS</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Computational &amp; Molecular Modeling</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Natural products--Analysis</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Cheminformatics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Chemistry--Data processing</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Vol. 2 of Chemoinformatics of Natural Products introduces the reader to the currently available tools for toxicity prediction, drug property prediction, an enumeration of compounds, scaffolds and functional groups in nature, computational methods for lead identification, metabolite biosynthesis, etc. Selected case studies and hands-on tutorial exercises have been included.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3290806&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="45">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3290805">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Self-Reinforced Polymer Composites : The Science, Engineering and Technology</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Padmanabhan Krishnan</au>
            <au>Sharan Chandran M</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>De Gruyter STEM</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110647297</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110647334</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110647402</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Self-Reinforced Polymer Composites : The Science, Engineering and Technology</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Padmanabhan Krishnan</au>
            <au>Sharan Chandran M</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Industrial &amp; Technical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Chemical &amp; Biochemical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Textiles &amp; Polymers</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Polymeric composites--Properties</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Polymeric composites</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This book is a comprehensive introduction to all aspects of self-reinforced polymer composites (SRCs) science and technology. After introducing the fundamental characteristics of SRCs, ample space is given to manufacturing, processing, characterization and application techniques. The approach is didactic and focused on formulations, illustrations and applications, which makes the book ideal for students, teachers and practitioners alike.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3290805&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="46">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3286770">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Mastering Python : Write Powerful and Efficient Code Using the Full Range of Python's Capabilities</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Rick van Hattem</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781800207721</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781800202108</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Packt Publishing</pub>
          <place>[S.l.]</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Mastering Python : Write Powerful and Efficient Code Using the Full Range of Python's Capabilities</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Rick van Hattem</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Languages / Python</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Python (Computer program language)</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Use advanced features of Python to write high-quality, readable code and packagesKey FeaturesExtensively updated for Python 3.10 with new chapters on design patterns, scientific programming, machine learning, and interactive PythonShape your scripts using key concepts like concurrency, performance optimization, asyncio, and multiprocessingLearn how advanced Python features fit together to produce maintainable codeBook DescriptionEven if you find writing Python code easy, writing code that is efficient, maintainable, and reusable is not so straightforward. Many of Python's capabilities are underutilized even by more experienced programmers. Mastering Python, Second Edition, is an authoritative guide to understanding advanced Python programming so you can write the highest quality code. This new edition has been extensively revised and updated with exercises, four new chapters and updates up to Python 3.10. Revisit important basics, including Pythonic style and syntax and functional programming. Avoid common mistakes made by programmers of all experience levels. Make smart decisions about the best testing and debugging tools to use, optimize your code's performance across multiple machines and Python versions, and deploy often-forgotten Python features to your advantage. Get fully up to speed with asyncio and stretch the language even further by accessing C functions with simple Python calls. Finally, turn your new-and-improved code into packages and share them with the wider Python community. If you are a Python programmer wanting to improve your code quality and readability, this Python book will make you confident in writing high-quality scripts and taking on bigger challengesWhat you will learnWrite beautiful Pythonic code and avoid common Python coding mistakesApply the power of decorators, generators, coroutines, and metaclassesUse different testing systems like pytest, unittest, and doctestTrack and optimize application performance for both memory and CPU usageDebug your applications with PDB, Werkzeug, and faulthandlerImprove your performance through asyncio, multiprocessing, and distributed computingExplore popular libraries like Dask, NumPy, SciPy, pandas, TensorFlow, and scikit-learnExtend Python's capabilities with C/C++ libraries and system callsWho this book is forThis book will benefit more experienced Python programmers who wish to upskill, serving as a reference for best practices and some of the more intricate Python techniques. Even if you have been using Python for years, chances are that you haven't yet encountered every topic discussed in this book. A good understanding of Python programming is necessary</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3286770&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="47">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3283569">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Endoscopic Lateral Skull Base Surgery : Principles, Anatomy, Approaches</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Daniele Marchioni</au>
            <au>Livio Presutti</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9783132412774</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783132414358</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783132582361</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Thieme</pub>
          <place>New York</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Endoscopic Lateral Skull Base Surgery : Principles, Anatomy, Approaches</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Daniele Marchioni</au>
            <au>Livio Presutti</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Otolaryngology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Surgery / Neurosurgery</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Skull base--Endoscopic surgery</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The quintessential state-of-the-art atlas on endoscopic approaches to the lateral skull baseThe endoscope has become a highly effective tool in the arsenal of ear and skull base surgeons. Endoscopic Lateral Skull Base Surgery: Principles, Anatomy, Approaches by endoscopic surgery masters Daniele Marchioni and Livio Presutti, reflects their development of innovative transcanalar approaches to the lateral cranial base using the external auditory canal as a surgical corridor. This unique atlas is designed to teach and clarify current and emerging endoscopic-assisted surgery approaches to the lateral skull base.The common goal of these cutting-edge procedures is to access and treat tumors located in the lateral cranial base via the most minimally-invasive endoscopic approach possible, thereby bypassing delicate cranial nerves, dural, cerebral, and vascular structures. Throughout 14 chapters, an impressive group of skull base surgeons share firsthand insights and expertise in areas vital to endoscopic skull base surgery.Key FeaturesFeaturing contributions from the who's who of global experts who continue to innovate by using the endoscope beyond its traditional use in middle ear surgeryOpening chapters cover anatomy, microscopic approaches, endoscopic dissection, instrumentation, OR set-up, and radiologic assessmentsProcedural chapters detail endoscopic approaches including transtemporal combined, retrosigmoid, and transcanalar techniques such as suprageniculate, transpromontorial, and infracochlearPatient cases, clinical applications, and step-by-step guidance enhance understanding of diverse endoscopic approachesHigh-quality preoperative, intraoperative, and postoperative illustrations are selected from thousands of surgeries performed by the authorsThis remarkable book provides the most comprehensive and elucidating information written to date on endoscopic approaches to the lateral skull base, making it essential reading for novice and expert surgeons alike.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3283569&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="48">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3277060">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Machine Learning in the Analysis and Forecasting of Financial Time Series</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Jaydip Sen, Editor</au>
            <au>Sidra Mehtab, Editor</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781527583245</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781527583252</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Cambridge Scholars Publishing</pub>
          <place>Newcastle-upon-Tyne</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Machine Learning in the Analysis and Forecasting of Financial Time Series</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Jaydip Sen, Editor</au>
            <au>Sidra Mehtab, Editor</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Econometrics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Artificial intelligence--Financial applications</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This book is a collection of real-world cases, illustrating how to handle challenging and volatile financial time series data for a better understanding of their past behavior and robust forecasting of their future movement. It demonstrates how the concepts and techniques of statistical, econometric, machine learning, and deep learning are applied to build robust predictive models, and the ways in which these models can be used for constructing profitable portfolios of investments. All the concepts and methods used here have been implemented using R and Python languages on TensorFlow and Keras frameworks. The book will be particularly useful for advanced postgraduate and doctoral students of finance, economics, econometrics, statistics, data science, computer science, and information technology.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3277060&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="49">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3277057">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>A Dictionary of Persian Grammar</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>A. Soheili, Author</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781527582538</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781527582545</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Cambridge Scholars Publishing</pub>
          <place>Newcastle upon Tyne</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>A Dictionary of Persian Grammar</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>A. Soheili, Author</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Grammar &amp; Punctuation</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">FOREIGN LANGUAGE STUDY / Persian</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">REFERENCE / Dictionaries</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Persian language--Grammar--Dictionaries</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This dictionary of Persian grammar has certain distinctive features that make it more informative and attractive than other sources on Persian grammar. Every entry here begins with a thorough linguistic analysis, according to the latest developments in the field, followed by its literary usage, which is an integral part of the language and culture. The final part of the book deals with the developmental stages of acquiring Persian, as clear evidence for the origins of the linguistic descriptions. The value of this dictionary lies in its use as a three tiered compilation that meets the needs and demands of both instructors of Persian and students of Persian language and linguistics.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3277057&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="50">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3262562">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Sustainable Natural Fiber Composites</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Khan, A.</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781644901847</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781644901854</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Materials Research Forum LLC</pub>
          <place>[S.l.]</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Sustainable Natural Fiber Composites</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Khan, A.</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Fibrous composites</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The book covers such diverse topics as cellulose fibers in cement paste and concrete, biodegradable materials for dental applications, coconut and pineapple fiber composites, biodegradable plastic composites, durability against fatigue and moisture, physical and mechanical characterization of fiber composites, improving the hydrophobic nature of fiber composites, and hybrid natural fiber composites. Keywords: Fiber Reinforced Composites, Biodegradable Composites, Polymethyl Methacrylate, Cellulose Fibers, Coconut Fibers, Biocomposites, Resol-Vegetable Fibers, Pineapple Natural Fiber Composite, Dental Applications, Cement Paste, Concrete, Thermoplasticity, Fatigue, Moisture, Thermal Conductivity.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3262562&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
</records>