
<records>
  <rec resultID="1">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3102881">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Rough Draft of History : A Century of US Social Movements in the News</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Edwin Amenta</au>
            <au>Neal Caren</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Princeton Studies in American Politics: Historical, International, and Comparative Perspectices</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9780691232775</isbn>
          <isbn type="print">9780691232782</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9780691232768</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Princeton University Press</pub>
          <place>Princeton, New Jersey</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Rough Draft of History : A Century of US Social Movements in the News</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Edwin Amenta</au>
            <au>Neal Caren</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Sociology / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">HISTORY / United States / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Political Ideologies / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Political Process / Political Advocacy</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Political Process / Media &amp; Internet</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Social movements--Press coverage--United States</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Social movements--United States--History</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>A comprehensive account of the media's coverage of social movements in the United StatesA new view of twentieth-century US social movements, Rough Draft of History examines how national newspapers covered social movements and the organizations driving them. Edwin Amenta and Neal Caren identify hundreds of movement organizations, from the Women's Christian Temperance Union to Occupy Wall Street, and document their treatment in the news. In doing so, Amenta and Caren provide an alternative account of US history from below, as it was refracted through journalistic lenses.Iconic organizations in the women's rights, African American civil rights, and environmental movements gained substantial media attention. But so too did now-forgotten groups, such as the German-American Alliance, Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies, and Peace and Freedom Party. Amenta and Caren show why some organizations made big news while others did not, why some were treated well while others were handled roughly. They recover forgotten stories, including that of the Townsend Plan, a Depression-era organization that helped establish Social Security. They also reveal that the media handled the civil rights movement far more harshly than popular histories recount. And they detail the difficulties movements face in today's brave new media world.Drawing from digitized newspapers across a century and through to the present, Rough Draft of History offers insights for those seeking social and political change and those trying to make sense of it.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3102881&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="2">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3063700">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Talking to the Girls : Intimate and Political Essays on the Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Edvige Giunta</au>
            <au>Mary Anne Trasciatti</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781613321508</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781613321539</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <ed>First edition</ed>
          <pub>New Village Press</pub>
          <place>[New York, New York]</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Talking to the Girls : Intimate and Political Essays on the Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Edvige Giunta</au>
            <au>Mary Anne Trasciatti</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Sociology / Urban</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">HISTORY / United States / 20th Century</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Women's Studies</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Clothing factories--New York (State)--New York</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Labor movement--New York (State)--New York</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Women immigrants--New York (State)--New York--Social conditions</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Candid and intimate accounts of the factory-worker tragedy that shaped American labor rights On March 25, 1911, a fire broke out on the eighth floor of the Asch Building in Greenwich Village, New York. The top three floors housed the Triangle Waist Company, a factory where approximately 500 workers, mostly young immigrant women and girls, labored to produce fashionable cotton blouses, known as “waists.” The fire killed 146 workers in a mere 15 minutes but pierced the perpetual conscience of citizens everywhere. The Asch Building had been considered a modern fireproof structure, but inadequate fire safety regulations left the workers inside unprotected. The tragedy of the fire, and the resulting movements for change, were pivotal in shaping workers'rights and unions. A powerful collection of diverse voices, Talking to the Girls: Intimate and Political Essays on the Triangle Fire brings together stories from writers, artists, activists, scholars, and family members of the Triangle workers. Nineteen contributors from across the globe speak of a singular event with remarkable impact. One hundred and eleven years after the tragic incident, Talking to the Girls articulates a story of contemporary global relevance and stands as an act of collective testimony: a written memorial to the Triangle victims.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3063700&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="3">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3063694">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Work Work Work : Labor, Alienation, and Class Struggle</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Michael D. Yates</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>MRP S22</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781583679654</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781583679685</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Monthly Review Press</pub>
          <place>New York</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Work Work Work : Labor, Alienation, and Class Struggle</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Michael D. Yates</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Labor &amp; Industrial Relations</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Labor / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Social classes</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Social conflict</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Working class</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Labor</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Work--Social aspects</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>A potent glimpse into the behind-the-scenes workplace control mechanisms which prevent workers from defending themselves from exploitationFor most economists, labor is simply a commodity, bought and sold in markets like any other – and what happens after that is not their concern. Individual prospective workers offer their services to individual employers, each acting solely out of self-interest and facing each other as equals. The forces of demand and supply operate so that there is neither a shortage nor a surplus of labor, and, in theory, workers and bosses achieve their respective ends. Michael D. Yates, in Work Work Work: Labor, Alienation, and Class Struggle, offers a vastly different take on the nature of the labor market.This book reveals the raw truth: The labor market is in fact a mere veil over the exploitation of workers. Peek behind it, and we clearly see the extraction, by a small but powerful class of productive property-owning capitalists, of a surplus from a much larger and propertyless class of wage laborers. Work Work Work offers us a glimpse into the mechanisms critical to this subterfuge: In every workplace, capital implements a comprehensive set of control mechanisms to constrain those who toil from defending themselves against exploitation. These include everything from the herding of workers into factories to the extreme forms of surveillance utilized by today's “captains of industry” like the Walton family (of the Walmart empire) and Jeff Bezos.In these strikingly lucid and passionately written chapters, Yates explains the reality of labor markets, the nature of work in capitalist societies, and the nature and necessity of class struggle, which alone can bring exploitation – and the system of control that makes it possible – to a final end.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3063694&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="4">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3058740">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Analyzing Telework, Trustworthiness, and Performance Using Leader-Member Exchange : COVID-19 Perspective</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Michael A. Brown Sr</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Human Resources Management and Organizational Development (AHRMOD) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799889502</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799889526</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799889533</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Analyzing Telework, Trustworthiness, and Performance Using Leader-Member Exchange : COVID-19 Perspective</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Michael A. Brown Sr</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Organizational Behavior</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Business Communication / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Organizational Development</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Telecommuting</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">COVID-19 Pandemic, 2020-</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>While the concept of teleworking has existed for many years, the COVID-19 pandemic drastically altered the operations of businesses and industries around the world. Through these shifts, there have been many challenges of adapting employees, business operations, productivity levels, technology, and more to meet this increased demand in teleworking. Through these challenges, not only were businesses forced to adapt, but a new wave of telework and its approach have been fostered. Analyzing Telework, Trustworthiness, and Performance Using Leader-Member Exchange: COVID-19 Perspective focuses on evaluating the response to the pandemic and how to continually improve teleworking and organizations in their utilization of remote work. This book provides multifaceted perspectives focused on all parties involved in these issues, from employees to CEOs. Covering topics such as employee risk, telework resistance, and performance, this book is an essential resource for managers, CEOs, business leaders, students of higher education, professors, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3058740&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="5">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3058737">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Advancements in the Processing, Characterization, and Application of Lightweight Materials</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Kaushik Kumar</au>
            <au>B. Sridhar Babu</au>
            <au>J. Paulo Davim</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Chemical and Materials Engineering (ACME) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799878643</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799878667</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799878674</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Advancements in the Processing, Characterization, and Application of Lightweight Materials</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Kaushik Kumar</au>
            <au>B. Sridhar Babu</au>
            <au>J. Paulo Davim</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Manufacturing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Lightweight materials</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>In the automotive industry, the need to reduce vehicle weight has given rise to extensive research efforts to develop aluminum and magnesium alloys for structural car body parts. In aerospace, the move toward composite airframe structures urged an increased use of formable titanium alloys. In steel research, there are ongoing efforts to design novel damage-controlled forming processes for a new generation of efficient and reliable lightweight steel components. All these materials, and more, constitute today's research mission for lightweight structures. They provide a fertile materials science research field aiming to achieve a better understanding of the interplay between industrial processing, microstructure development, and the resulting material properties. The Handbook of Research on Advancements in the Processing, Characterization, and Application of Lightweight Materials provides the recent advancements in the lightweight mat materials processing, manufacturing, and characterization. This book identifies the need for modern tools and techniques for designing lightweight materials and addresses multidisciplinary approaches for applying their use. Covering topics such as numerical optimization, fatigue characterization, and process evaluation, this text is an essential resource for materials engineers, manufacturers, practitioners, engineers, academicians, chief research officers, researchers, students, and vice presidents of research in government, industry, and academia.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3058737&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="6">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3032367">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Work Pray Code : When Work Becomes Religion in Silicon Valley</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Carolyn Chen</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9780691219080</isbn>
          <isbn type="print">9780691220888</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9780691220871</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Princeton University Press</pub>
          <place>Princeton</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Work Pray Code : When Work Becomes Religion in Silicon Valley</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Carolyn Chen</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Sociology / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Human Resources &amp; Personnel Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Programming / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BODY, MIND &amp; SPIRIT / Mindfulness &amp; Meditation</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">RELIGION / Spirituality</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Sociology of Religion</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Religion in the workplace--California--Santa Clara Valley (Santa Clara County)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">High technology industries--California--Santa Clara Valley (Santa Clara County)--Employees</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Corporate culture--California--Santa Clara Valley (Santa Clara County)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Employees--Religious life</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>How tech giants are reshaping spirituality to serve their religion of peak productivitySilicon Valley is known for its lavish perks, intense work culture, and spiritual gurus. Work Pray Code explores how tech companies are bringing religion into the workplace in ways that are replacing traditional places of worship, blurring the line between work and religion and transforming the very nature of spiritual experience in modern life.Over the past forty years, highly skilled workers have been devoting more time and energy to their jobs than ever before. They are also leaving churches, synagogues, and temples in droves—but they have not abandoned religion. Carolyn Chen spent more than five years in Silicon Valley, conducting a wealth of in-depth interviews and gaining unprecedented access to the best and brightest of the tech world. The result is a penetrating account of how work now satisfies workers'needs for belonging, identity, purpose, and transcendence that religion once met. Chen argues that tech firms are offering spiritual care such as Buddhist-inspired mindfulness practices to make their employees more productive, but that our religious traditions, communities, and public sphere are paying the price.We all want our jobs to be meaningful and fulfilling. Work Pray Code reveals what can happen when work becomes religion, and when the workplace becomes the institution that shapes our souls.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3032367&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="7">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3026437">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Management of Complications in Common Hand and Wrist Procedures : FESSH Instructional Course Book 2021</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Brigitte van der Heijden</au>
            <au>Jan-Ragnar Haugstvedt</au>
            <au>Henk Coert</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9783132436039</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783132436046</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783132436053</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Thieme</pub>
          <place>Stuttgart</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Management of Complications in Common Hand and Wrist Procedures : FESSH Instructional Course Book 2021</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Brigitte van der Heijden</au>
            <au>Jan-Ragnar Haugstvedt</au>
            <au>Henk Coert</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Surgery / Cosmetic &amp; Reconstructive</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Orthopedics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Wrist--Wounds and injuries--Treatment--Complications</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Hand--Wounds and injuries--Treatment--Complications</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Management of Complications in Common Hand and Wrist Procedures: FESSH Instructional Course Book 2021Operative complications can have a major impact on patients and surgeons. While most textbooks list them, few provide in-depth discussion on prevention, repercussions, and methods to resolve them. Management of Complications in Common Hand and Wrist Procedures: FESSH Instructional Course Book 2021, edited by renowned hand surgeons Brigitte van der Heijden, Jan-Ragnar Haugstvedt, and Henk Coert, features contributions from an impressive group of international hand surgery experts.This book provides in-depth, illustrated coverage on the prevention and management of complications that can occur during common hand and wrist approaches. It also provides insights on how meticulously performed hand therapy can help alleviate postsurgical problems, on the complex regional pain syndrome (CRPS), and on critical social issues.Key HighlightsFirsthand clinical pearls, evidence-based interventions, and expert opinion for preventing and resolving complications from distinguished hand surgery expertsThe history of the catch-all term CRPS, why continued use of this term is a disservice to patients and medical progress, and an evidence-based argument on why it should be removed from the armamentarium and eventually the literatureManaging expectations of patients with factitious disorders, the role of informed consent in preventing medicolegal issues, and the impact of complications on surgeons and patientsThis unique and insightful resource will be invaluable in the practice of plastic, orthopaedic, and trauma surgeons specializing in hand and wrist surgery.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3026437&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="8">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="2974393">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>The Digital Factory : The Human Labor of Automation</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Moritz Altenried</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9780226815480</isbn>
          <isbn type="print">9780226815497</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9780226815503</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>University of Chicago Press</pub>
          <place>Chicago</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>The Digital Factory : The Human Labor of Automation</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Moritz Altenried</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Labor / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Workplace Culture</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Labor &amp; Industrial Relations</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Sociology / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SOCIAL SCIENCE / Media Studies</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Automation</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Social Aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Industrial management--Technological innovations</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Technological innovations--Social aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Technological innovations--Economic aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Unskilled labor</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Internet industry--Employees</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">High technology industries--Employees</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Assembly-line methods</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The Digital Factory reveals the hidden human labor that supports today's digital capitalism. The workers of today's digital factory include those in Amazon warehouses, delivery drivers, Chinese gaming workers, Filipino content moderators, and rural American search engine optimizers. Repetitive yet stressful, boring yet often emotionally demanding, these jobs require little formal qualification, but can demand a large degree of skills and knowledge. This work is often hidden behind the supposed magic of algorithms and thought to be automated, but it is in fact highly dependent on human labor. The workers of today's digital factory are not as far removed from a typical auto assembly line as we might think. Moritz Altenried takes us inside today's digital factories, showing that they take very different forms, including gig economy platforms, video games, and Amazon warehouses. As Altenried shows, these digital factories often share surprising similarities with factories from the industrial age. As globalized capitalism and digital technology continue to transform labor around the world, Altenried offers a timely and poignant exploration of how these changes are restructuring the social division of labor and its geographies as well as the stratifications and lines of struggle.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=2974393&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="9">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="2961869">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Governance and Business Models for Sustainable Capitalism</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Atle Midttun</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Routledge Studies in Management, Organizations and Society</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9780367770440</isbn>
          <isbn type="print">9781138210592</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781315454917</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781315454924</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781315454931</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Routledge</pub>
          <place>New York, NY</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Governance and Business Models for Sustainable Capitalism</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Atle Midttun</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Corporate Governance</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Business Ethics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Social responsibility of business</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Capitalism</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Sustainability</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Governance and Business Models for Sustainable Capitalism touches upon many of the central themes of today's debate on business and society. In particular, it brings attention to a recurrent tension between efficiency, innovation, and productivity on the one hand, and fairness, equity, and sustainability on the other. The book argues that we need radical rethinking of business models and economic governance, beyond the classical doctrine, which sees social and ecological responsibility as lying with public-policy regulation of purely profit-seeking firms. In spite of the popular CSR agenda, business – as we know it today – is both too transient and too limited in its motivation to carry the regulatory burden. We need to adopt a much wider concept of'partnered governance', where advanced states and pioneering companies work together to raise the social and environmental bar. The book suggests that civil engagements based on moral rather than formal rights, and amplified through the media, may provide a healthy challenge both to autocratic planning and to solely profit-centered commercialization. The book also proposes a triple cycle theory of innovation for sustainability: a novel framing of the efficacy of green and prosocial entrepreneurship as intertwined with political visions and supportive institutions. In addition, the book offers reflections on the ways in which further digital robotizaton may enable transition to an ‘Agora Economy'where productive efficiency is combined with expanded civic freedoms. Aimed primarily at researchers, academics, and students in the fields of political economy, business and society, corporate governance, business ethics, corporate social responsibility, and sustainability, the book will additionally be of value to practitioners, supplying them with information regarding the challenges associated with the shaping of sustainable or ‘civilised'market capitalism for a better world.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=2961869&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="10">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="2904934">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Beyond Leviathan : Critique of the State</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>István Mészáros</au>
            <au>John Bellamy Foster</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781583679500</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781583679524</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Monthly Review Press</pub>
          <place>New York</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Beyond Leviathan : Critique of the State</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>István Mészáros</au>
            <au>John Bellamy Foster</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / Hermeneutics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Political Ideologies / Communism, Post-Communism &amp; Socialism</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Political Economy</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Political science--Philosophy</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Political science--History</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>A field-defining masterwork, this posthumous publication maps the evolution of the idea of the state from ancient Greece to today István Mészáros was one of the greatest political theorists of the twentieth century. Left unfinished at the time of his death, Beyond Leviathan is written on the magisterial scale of his previous book, Beyond Capital, and meant to complement that work. It focuses on the transcendence of the state, along with the transcendence of capital and alienated labor, while traversing the history of political theory from Plato to the present. Aristotle, More, Machiavelli, and Vico are only a few of the thinkers discussed in depth. The larger objective of this work is no less than to develop a full-edged critique of the state, in the Marxian tradition, and set against the critique of capital. Not only does it provide, for the first time, an all-embracing Marxian theory of the state, it gives new political meaning to the notion of “the withering away of the state.” In his definitive, seminal work, Mészáros seeks to illuminate the political preconditions for a society of substantive equality and substantive democracy.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=2904934&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="11">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3409451">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>New Approaches to Data Analytics and Internet of Things Through Digital Twin</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>P. Karthikeyan</au>
            <au>Polinpapilinho F. Katina</au>
            <au>S.P. Anandaraj</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781668457221</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668457245</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668457252</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>New Approaches to Data Analytics and Internet of Things Through Digital Twin</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>P. Karthikeyan</au>
            <au>Polinpapilinho F. Katina</au>
            <au>S.P. Anandaraj</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Database Administration &amp; Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Data Science / Data Analytics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Internet of Things (IoT)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Data mining</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Digital twins (Computer simulation)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Internet of things</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Even though many data analytics tools have been developed in the past years, their usage in the field of cyber twin warrants new approaches that consider various aspects including unified data representation, zero-day attack detection, data sharing across threat detection systems, real-time analysis, sampling, dimensionality reduction, resource-constrained data processing, and time series analysis for anomaly detection. Further study is required to fully understand the opportunities, benefits, and difficulties of data analytics and the internet of things in today's modern world. New Approaches to Data Analytics and Internet of Things Through Digital Twin considers how data analytics and the internet of things can be used successfully within the field of digital twin as well as the potential future directions of these technologies. Covering key topics such as edge networks, deep learning, intelligent data analytics, and knowledge discovery, this reference work is ideal for computer scientists, industry professionals, researchers, scholars, practitioners, academicians, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3409451&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="12">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3402049">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Biochemical Changes in Disease</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Inês Lopes Cardoso, Editor</au>
            <au>Fernanda Leal, Editor</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781527588745</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781527588752</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Cambridge Scholars Publishing</pub>
          <place>Newcastle-upon-Tyne</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Biochemical Changes in Disease</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Inês Lopes Cardoso, Editor</au>
            <au>Fernanda Leal, Editor</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Chemical &amp; Biochemical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Biochemistry</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Clinical biochemistry</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This book explores and identifies the main biochemical changes that occur in several diseases, including those of pancreatic, cardiovascular, musculoskeletal, psychiatric, nutritional, and infectious origin. It also considers the recognition of possible biochemical markers of each disease, highlighting how they can be used in diagnosis.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3402049&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="13">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3402036">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Versatile Precursors in Organic Synthesis</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Okram Mukherjee Singh, Author</au>
            <au>Thokchom Prasanta Singh, Author</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781527588660</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781527588677</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Cambridge Scholars Publishing</pub>
          <place>Newcastle upon Tyne, UK</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Versatile Precursors in Organic Synthesis</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Okram Mukherjee Singh, Author</au>
            <au>Thokchom Prasanta Singh, Author</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Organic</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Organic compounds--Synthesis</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This book elaborates on the synthesis of versatile precursors and their applications in organic synthesis through a systematic approach. It shows that understanding the chemical properties of different types of versatile building blocks is essential for the successful execution of organic synthesis. The text also discusses how a particular type of precursor is used in the preparation of different types of simple and complex organic compounds, depending on reaction conditions and other substrates.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3402036&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="14">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3394234">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Language Families in Contact : The Mutual Impact of Slavic and Romani</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Anna-Maria Sonnemann</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Language Contact and Bilingualism</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110756043</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110756173</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110756241</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00024</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter Mouton</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Language Families in Contact : The Mutual Impact of Slavic and Romani</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Anna-Maria Sonnemann</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">FOREIGN LANGUAGE STUDY / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Languages in contact--Europe</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Romani language</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Slavic languages--Influence on Romani</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Romani language--Foreign words and phrases</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Slavic languages--Foreign words and phrases</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Slavic languages</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The book provides an encyclopaedic overview of the language contact between Slavic languages and Romani in Eastern, South-Eastern and East-Central Europe. It is based on Yaron Matras'pragmatic-functional approach to language contact and follows a new direction in Romani linguistics that conceives Romani as a subgroup of closely related languages rather than a single language. The central topics discussed in the book are: Slavic impact on Romani phonetics and phonology, morphology and syntax; forms and functions of Slavic verbal prefixes in Romani; Slavic impact on the Romani lexicon; Romani elements in the nonstandard lexicon of the Slavic languages; writing Romani with ‘Slavic'alphabets.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3394234&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="15">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3387646">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Activating Middle Executives’ Agency to Lead and Manage During Times of Crisis</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Ann-Marie Wilmot</au>
            <au>Canute Sylvester Thompson</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Logistics, Operations, and Management Science (ALOMS) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668443316</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668443323</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668443330</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Activating Middle Executives’ Agency to Lead and Manage During Times of Crisis</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Ann-Marie Wilmot</au>
            <au>Canute Sylvester Thompson</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Leadership</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management Science</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">School crisis management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">School management and organization</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Educational leadership</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The role of lead executives is demanding under normal circumstances, but more so during times of institutional crisis. The existence of ongoing internal organizational crises plus crises triggered by external events and shocks requires that leaders and managers be equipped with the tools to manage such crises. Therefore, further study is required that considers the difficulties of leading various organizations as well as best practices for future management. The Handbook of Research on Activating Middle Executives'Agency to Lead and Manage During Times of Crisis is a comprehensive reference source that offers practical applications, tools, and skills to equip middle leaders to meaningfully participate in crisis management and resolution in institutions for improved outcomes and discusses a multi-pronged framework for building middle leaders'crisis response efficacies. The book also invites top-tier educational and industry practitioners to reflect on how they have led during times of crisis. Covering topics such as mentoring, coping strategies, and sustainable development, this major reference work is ideal for educational leaders, managers, business owners, human resource professionals, scholars, researchers, academicians, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3387646&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="16">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3387650">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Isolation, Characterization, and Therapeutic Applications of Natural Bioactive Compounds</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Ajeet Singh</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Bioinformatics and Biomedical Engineering (ABBE) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668473375</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668473382</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668473399</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Medical Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Isolation, Characterization, and Therapeutic Applications of Natural Bioactive Compounds</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Ajeet Singh</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Alternative &amp; Complementary Medicine</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Pharmacology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Research</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Phytochemicals--Purification</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Phytochemicals--Therapeutic use</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Medicinal plants</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Natural products have historically been key to drug discovery and therapeutic applications throughout many societies. In the modern era, natural bioactive compounds can be isolated, and their effects can be further studied for more successful outcomes. It is essential to study these natural bioactive compounds to enhance pharmaceuticals and drug discovery. Isolation, Characterization, and Therapeutic Applications of Natural Bioactive Compounds examines the applications of natural bioactive compounds from a health perspective. It discusses medicinal and therapeutic applications of natural bioactive molecules as well as the biological activities of different natural products and their properties. Covering topics such as drug discovery, government regulations, and phytochemical extraction, this premier reference source is an excellent resource for pharmacists, medical practitioners, phytologists, hospital administrators, government officials, faculty and students of higher education, librarians, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3387650&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="17">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3387651">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Perspectives of Management Accounting for Sustainable Business Practices</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Ionica Oncioiu</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781668445952</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668445976</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668445983</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Perspectives of Management Accounting for Sustainable Business Practices</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Ionica Oncioiu</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Accounting / Managerial</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Accounting / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Sustainable development</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Business enterprises--Environmental aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Managerial accounting</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>In the 21st century, management accounting gains new dimensions, expanding its research area. Additionally, management of sustainable performance is one of the phenomena faced by the current business environment, and in particular management corporations. The focus of management on profitability remains the main objective of any company, but it must also take into account the sustainability of social, economic, and environmental aspects. Under these circumstances, managerial decisions must be adjusted and strongly substantiated considering the information required by internal and external stakeholders including financial reporting. The information requirements of customers and other stakeholders are steadily increasing, and some companies face certain problems in implementing the concept of sustainability and environmental reporting. Perspectives of Management Accounting for Sustainable Business Practices proposes an interdisciplinary perspective and explores various theoretical and practical approaches to management accounting and its impact in the 21st century on different areas of activity. It contrasts external financial accounting for government regulators and the investment community with internal management accounting for managers to leverage decision making. Covering topics such as corporate social responsibility, disclosure issues, and performance analysis, this premier reference source is an essential resource for business leaders and executives, accountants, financial controllers, business analysts, budgeting managers, students and faculty of higher education, librarians, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3387651&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="18">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3380198">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Finance for Sustainability in a Turbulent Economy</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Abdul Rafay</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Finance, Accounting, and Economics (AFAE) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668455807</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668455821</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668455838</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Finance for Sustainability in a Turbulent Economy</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Abdul Rafay</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Green Business</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Corporate Finance / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Finance / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Sustainable development--Finance</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Finance--Environmental aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Clean energy industries--Finance</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Climate change and the depletion of resources will have a long-lasting effect on the globe. Thus, it is essential that businesses and organizations across the world adopt financial practices and strategies that allow them to continue their service, limit emissions, and preserve resources. However, these practices are only made more difficult to adopt within the context of a turbulent economy. In this context, it is imperative to research financial strategies to protect the environment and support business resilience. Finance for Sustainability in a Turbulent Economy provides international financial strategies to achieve sustainable business practices within a turbulent economy. It highlights the importance of maintaining environmental health in a cost-effective way. Covering topics such as environmental finance, renewable energy frameworks, and social responsibility, this premier reference source is an essential resource for environmental scientists, government officials, engineers, business executives, environmentalists, politicians, students and educators of higher education, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3380198&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="19">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3380199">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Applications of Machine Learning and Deep Learning for Privacy and Cybersecurity</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Victor Lobo</au>
            <au>Anacleto Correia</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Information Security, Privacy, and Ethics (AISPE) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799894308</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799894322</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799894339</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Applications of Machine Learning and Deep Learning for Privacy and Cybersecurity</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Victor Lobo</au>
            <au>Anacleto Correia</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Security / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Security / Cryptography &amp; Encryption</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Data Science / Machine Learning</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Deep learning (Machine learning)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Computer networks--Security measures--Data processing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Computer security</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The growth of innovative cyber threats, many based on metamorphosing techniques, has led to security breaches and the exposure of critical information in sites that were thought to be impenetrable. The consequences of these hacking actions were, inevitably, privacy violation, data corruption, or information leaking. Machine learning and data mining techniques have significant applications in the domains of privacy protection and cybersecurity, including intrusion detection, authentication, and website defacement detection, that can help to combat these breaches. Applications of Machine Learning and Deep Learning for Privacy and Cybersecurity provides machine and deep learning methods for analysis and characterization of events regarding privacy and anomaly detection as well as for establishing predictive models for cyber attacks or privacy violations. It provides case studies of the use of these techniques and discusses the expected future developments on privacy and cybersecurity applications. Covering topics such as behavior-based authentication, machine learning attacks, and privacy preservation, this book is a crucial resource for IT specialists, computer engineers, industry professionals, privacy specialists, security professionals, consultants, researchers, academicians, and students and educators of higher education.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3380199&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="20">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3380196">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Advancements in Quantum Blockchain With Real-Time Applications</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Mahendra Kumar Shrivas</au>
            <au>Kamal Kant Hiran</au>
            <au>Ashok Bhansali</au>
            <au>Ruchi Doshi</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Data Mining and Database Management (ADMDM) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781668450727</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668450741</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668450758</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA, USA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Advancements in Quantum Blockchain With Real-Time Applications</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Mahendra Kumar Shrivas</au>
            <au>Kamal Kant Hiran</au>
            <au>Ashok Bhansali</au>
            <au>Ruchi Doshi</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Database Administration &amp; Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Blockchain</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Quantum Computing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Blockchains (Databases)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Quantum computing</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The amalgamation of post-quantum cryptography in cyber-physical systems makes the computing system secure and also generates opportunities in areas like smart contracts, quantum blockchain, and smart security solutions. Sooner or later, all computing and security systems are going to adopt quantum-proof cryptography to safeguard these systems from quantum attacks. Post-quantum cryptography has tremendous potential in various domains and must be researched and explored further to be utilized successfully. Advancements in Quantum Blockchain With Real-Time Applications considers various concepts of computing such as quantum computing, post-quantum cryptography, quantum attack-resistant blockchain, quantum blockchains, and multidisciplinary applications and real-world use cases. The book also discusses solutions to various real-world problems within the industry. Covering key topics such as cybersecurity, data management, and smart society, this reference work is ideal for computer scientists, industry professionals, academicians, practitioners, scholars, researchers, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3380196&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="21">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3368154">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Contemporary Approaches to Legal Linguistics</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Daniel Green, Luke Green (Eds.)</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9783643913876</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783643963871</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>LIT Verlag</pub>
          <place>ZURICH</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Contemporary Approaches to Legal Linguistics</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Daniel Green, Luke Green (Eds.)</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">LAW / Comparative</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Law--Language--Congresses</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>In this volume, scholars explore and discuss current issues in Theoretical Legal Linguistics (TLL) and Applied Legal Linguistics (ALL), contributing to the growing body of international research in the field. Focus is placed on the interconnected skills, tasks and approaches to the study of legal language in its plethora of facets as presented at the first international conference and the second International Legal Linguistics Workshop (ILLWS19) of the Austrian Association for Legal Linguistics. The articles present research in the areas of contract interpretation, bijuralism, the European Reference Language System, clear language and communication in legal settings, issues in legal semantics, plain legal language in multilingual legislative drafting, legal language teaching, light verb constructions in legal German, forensic linguistic expert testimony, deontic modality in legislative drafting, migration and legal language, appeals in Russian and their qualification as language crimes, and graduation in the use of force statutes. The concepts, methods, and findings offer valuable insights into current research in legal linguistics.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3368154&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="22">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3365809">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Introduction</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Frank Rösch</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Nuclear- and Radiochemistry</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110742718</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110742725</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110742800</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00001</vid>
          <ed>2nd, extended edition</ed>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Introduction</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Frank Rösch</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Radiology, Radiotherapy &amp; Nuclear Medicine</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Analytic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Inorganic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Physical &amp; Theoretical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Industrial &amp; Technical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Energy</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Physics / Nuclear</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Radiochemistry</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Nuclear chemistry</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Nuclear chemistry represents a vital fi eld of basic and applied research. This Volume 1 Nuclear- and Radiochemistry: Introduction describes the relevant parameters of stable and unstable atomic nuclei, the various modes of radioactive transformations, the corresponding types of radiation, and fi nally the mechanisms of nuclear reactions. The 2nd edition has updated the chapters throughout with additional material. The reader is also referred to the new edition of Volume 2 Nuclear- and Radiochemistry: Modern Applications.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3365809&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="23">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3365808">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Modern Applications</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Frank Rösch</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Nuclear- and Radiochemistry</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110742671</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110742701</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110742794</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00002</vid>
          <ed>2nd, extended edition</ed>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Modern Applications</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Frank Rösch</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Radiology, Radiotherapy &amp; Nuclear Medicine</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Analytic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Inorganic</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Physical &amp; Theoretical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Industrial &amp; Technical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Energy</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Physics / Nuclear</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Radiochemistry</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Nuclear chemistry</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Modern applications of nuclear chemistry concern various scientific disciplines. This new edition of Volume 2 Nuclear- and Radiochemistry: Modern Applications summarizes recent knowledge on radiation measurement and dosimetry, highsensitive, high-selective, and non-destructive analytical technologies, environmental aspects and nuclear dating, state-of-the-art research on actinides and radioelements, nuclear energy, and molecular diagnosis and patient treatment for nuclear medicine. Individual topics are presented by leading experts. This 2nd edition has updated literature references and includes new material throughout. The reader is also referred to the new edition of Volume 1 Nuclear- and Radiochemistry: Introduction.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3365808&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="24">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3347553">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Thinking Through Technology : The Path Between Engineering and Philosophy</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Carl Mitcham</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9780226531960</isbn>
          <isbn type="print">9780226531984</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9780226825397</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>University of Chicago Press</pub>
          <place>Chicago</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Thinking Through Technology : The Path Between Engineering and Philosophy</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Carl Mitcham</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Philosophie</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Technology--Philosophy</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>What does it mean to think about technology philosophically? Why try? These are the issues that Carl Mitcham addresses in this work, a comprehensive, critical introduction to the philosophy of technology and a discussion of its sources and uses. Tracing the changing meaning of'technology'from ancient times to our own, Mitcham identifies the most important traditions of critical analysis of technology: the engineering approach, which assumes the centrality of technology in human life; and the humanities approach, which is concerned with its moral and cultural boundaries. Mitcham bridges these two traditions through an analysis of discussions of engineering design, of the distinction between tools and machines, and of engineering science itself. He looks at technology as it is experienced in everyday life—as material objects (from kitchenware to computers), as knowledge ( including recipes, rules, theories, and intuitive'know-how'), as activity (design, construction, and use), and as volition (knowing how to use technology and understanding its consequences). By elucidating these multiple aspects, Mitcham establishes criteria for a more comprehensive analysis of ethical issues in applications of science and technology. This book will guide anyone wanting to reflect on technology and its moral implications.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3347553&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="25">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3344510">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Persons of the Market : Conservatism, Corporate Personhood, and Economic Theology</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Kevin Musgrave</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781611864335</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781609177034</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781628954715</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Michigan State University Press</pub>
          <place>East Lansing, Michigan</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Persons of the Market : Conservatism, Corporate Personhood, and Economic Theology</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Kevin Musgrave</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Rhetoric</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Political Economy</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">RELIGION / Christian Theology / History</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Liberalism</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Capitalism--Religious aspects--Christianity</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Taking corporate personhood as a starting point, Persons of the Market observes the complex historical entanglement of Christian theology and liberal capitalism to shed new light on their seemingly odd marriage in contemporary American politics. Author Kevin Musgrave highlights the ways that theories of corporate and human personhood have long been and remain bound together by examining four case studies: the U.S. Supreme Court's 1886 Santa Clara decision, the role of early twentieth-century advertisers in endowing corporations with souls, Justice Lewis Powell Jr.'s eponymous memo of 1971, and the arc of the conservative movement from Ronald Reagan to Donald Trump. Tracing this rhetorical history of the extension and attribution of personhood to the corporate form illustrates how the corporation has for many increasingly become a normative model or ideal to which human persons should aspire. In closing, the book offers preliminary ideas about how we might fashion a more democratic and humane understanding of what it means to be a person.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3344510&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="26">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3338099">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Second Language Acquisition Theory : The Legacy of Professor Michael H. Long</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Alessandro G. Benati</au>
            <au>John W. Schwieter</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Bilingual Processing and Acquisition (BPA)</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9789027212566</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9789027257482</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00014</vid>
          <pub>John Benjamins Publishing Company</pub>
          <place>Amsterdam</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Second Language Acquisition Theory : The Legacy of Professor Michael H. Long</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Alessandro G. Benati</au>
            <au>John W. Schwieter</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Study &amp; Teaching</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Second language acquisition</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Professor Michael H. Long (1945-2021) was one of the most influential scholars in the field of second language acquisition. This volume presents a set of chapters that honour some of his key contributions in language teaching and learning. Following a bibliometric analysis of the impact of his research to the field, the volume spans topics such as task-based language teaching, focus on form, age effects, transfer, feedback, interaction, incidental learning, stabilization, among many others.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3338099&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="27">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3318999">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>New Directions in Organizational and Management History</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Sonia Coman</au>
            <au>Andrea Casey</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>De Gruyter Studies in Organizational and Management History</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110720419</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110693539</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110720440</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00001</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>New Directions in Organizational and Management History</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Sonia Coman</au>
            <au>Andrea Casey</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Organizational Behavior</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Organizational Development</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Organizational effectiveness</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This book provides a valuable review of the disciplines of organizational and management history, illuminating the interconnectedness of these disciplines, identifying gaps in the literature, and sketching a model for a unified field of research and study. This co-authored study is a long-awaited theoretical re-evaluation of organizational and management history. The authors explore the disciplinary advantages of a joint approach to these related fields, noting opportunities for future scholarship, from the wider range of industries and case types to the richer theoretical toolbox. Within this framework, the book investigates interdisciplinary methodologies and surveys and analyzes the most promising of the newest theoretical lenses and empirical approaches in the field. The authors address complex issues from a metacritical perspective, from the emergent theorization of time in the context of organizational identity to the conundrum of case selection for empirical studies. Clear and thorough, the volume creates a compelling theoretical framework for future studies. New Directions in Organizational and Management History inaugurates, and sets the stage for, the new series De Gruyter Studies in Organizational and Management History.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3318999&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="28">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3319009">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Process Intensification : By Reactive and Membrane-assisted Separations</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Mirko Skiborowski</au>
            <au>Andrzej Górak</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>De Gruyter STEM</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110720457</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110720464</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110720600</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <ed>Second edition</ed>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Process Intensification : By Reactive and Membrane-assisted Separations</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Mirko Skiborowski</au>
            <au>Andrzej Górak</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Chemical &amp; Biochemical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Industrial Technology</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Membrane separation</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Chemical processes</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Process intensifi cation aims for increasing effi ciency and sustainability of (bio-)chemical production processes. This book presents strategies for the intensifi cation of fluid separation processes such as reactive distillation, reactive absorption and membrane assisted separations. The authors discuss theoretical fundamentals, model development, methods for synthesis and the design as well as scale-up and industrial process applications.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3319009&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="29">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3318994">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>How to Create High-performing Innovation Teams</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Mikael Johnsson</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9783110737110</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110731934</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110732016</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>How to Create High-performing Innovation Teams</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Mikael Johnsson</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Organizational Development</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / Business Development</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Entrepreneurship</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Leadership</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Organizational change</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Teams in the workplace</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Effective team work is essential if innovation projects are to succeed. How to create high-performing innovation teams provides practical guidance and advice on how to create high-performing teams regardless of type or size of company, organization, or public institution. It offers the reader pivotal tools and insights to use in practice. Both the theory and practice for creating high-performing innovation teams are discussed and new tools and insights are provided for managers, consultants, and academics. It answers the call for rapid innovation to respond to the increasingly changing market and to shorter product life cycles. How to create high-performing innovation teams addresses specifically the factors that enable innovation work from the perspective of the organization, the innovation team, and its members. In addition to co-located innovation teams, the book also discusses the differences among global organizations and what to consider in the creation of global high-performing innovation teams.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3318994&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="30">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3318989">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Advanced Mathematics : An Invitation in Preparation for Graduate School</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Patrick Guidotti</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>De Gruyter Textbook</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110780857</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110780925</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110780987</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Advanced Mathematics : An Invitation in Preparation for Graduate School</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Patrick Guidotti</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MATHEMATICS / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MATHEMATICS / Number Systems</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MATHEMATICS / Set Theory</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MATHEMATICS / Probability &amp; Statistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MATHEMATICS / Differential Equations / Ordinary</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MATHEMATICS / Differential Equations / Partial</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MATHEMATICS / Optimization</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Mathematics</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This exploration of a selection of fundamental topics and general purpose tools provides a roadmap to undergraduate students who yearn for a deeper dive into many of the concepts and ideas they have been encountering in their classes whether their motivation is pure curiosity or preparation for graduate studies. The topics intersect a wide range of areas encompassing both pure and applied mathematics. The emphasis and style of the book are motivated by the goal of developing self-reliance and independent mathematical thought. Mathematics requires both intuition and common sense as well as rigorous, formal argumentation. This book attempts to showcase both, simultaneously encouraging readers to develop their own insights and understanding and the adoption of proof writing skills. The most satisfying proofs/arguments are fully rigorous and completely intuitive at the same time.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3318989&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="31">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3306840">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Corpus Pragmatic Studies on the History of Medical Discourse</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Turo Hiltunen</au>
            <au>Irma Taavitsainen</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Pragmatics &amp; Beyond New Series (P&amp;BNS)</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9789027211101</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9789027257741</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00330</vid>
          <pub>John Benjamins Publishing Company</pub>
          <place>Amsterdam</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Corpus Pragmatic Studies on the History of Medical Discourse</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Turo Hiltunen</au>
            <au>Irma Taavitsainen</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / Pragmatics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Corpora (Linguistics)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Pragmatics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Medicine--Europe--History</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Medical writing--History</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Medical literature--History</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Medicine--Terminology</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The original studies in this volume provide new insights into the history of medical discourse across centuries in both professional and lay texts. The central themes deal with changes in medical writing in various societal and cultural contexts in search for best practices in corpus pragmatics for future work. Some studies apply quantitative methods of corpus linguistics and Digital Humanities, others adopt a qualitative, discourse-analytical perspective, focusing on particular texts, authors or medical topics, or specific functionally-defined discourse forms such as narratives. Quantitative and qualitative approaches are mutually complementary and shed light on different aspects of historical medical discourse. The methodologies aim at establishing validity and reliability for pragmatic analysis, taking into account relevant contextual factors and insights from other fields, such as medical and social history, history of ideas, and science studies.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3306840&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="32">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3305596">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Hannah Arendt and the History of Thought</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Marguerite La Caze</au>
            <au>Daniel Brennan</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Continental Philosophy and the History of Thought</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781666900859</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781666900866</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Lexington Books</pub>
          <place>Lanham</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Hannah Arendt and the History of Thought</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Marguerite La Caze</au>
            <au>Daniel Brennan</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / History &amp; Surveys / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / History &amp; Theory</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">PHILOSOPHY / Movements / Critical Theory</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Political science--Philosophy--History--20th century</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Philosophy, Modern--20th century</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Jewish women philosophers--Germany--Biography</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Hannah Arendt and the History of Thought, edited by Daniel Brennan and Marguerite La Caze, enrichens and deepens scholarship on Arendt's relation to philosophical history and traditions. Some contributors analyze thinkers not often linked to Arendt, such as William Shakespeare, Hans Jonas, and Simone de Beauvoir. Other contributors treat themes that are pressing and crucial to understanding Arendt's work, such as love in its many forms, ethnicity and race, disability, human rights, politics, and statelessness. The collection is anchored by chapters on Arendt's interpretation of Kant and her relation to early German Romanticism and phenomenology, while other chapters explore new perspectives, such as Arendt and film, her philosophical connections with other women thinkers, and her influence on Eastern European thought and activism. The collection expands the frames of reference for research on Arendt—both in terms of using a broader range of texts like her Denktagebuch and in examining her ideas about judgment, feminism, and worldliness in this wider context.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3305596&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="33">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3303420">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Intensification in English and Spanish Communication</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Nydia Flores-Ferrán</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781793639615</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781793639622</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Lexington Books</pub>
          <place>Lanham</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Intensification in English and Spanish Communication</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Nydia Flores-Ferrán</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / Sociolinguistics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Communication Studies</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / Pragmatics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Spanish language--Intensification</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">English language--Social aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">English language--Intensification</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Pragmatics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Spanish language--Social aspects</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>In this book, Nydia Flores-Ferrán offers a comprehensive examination of linguistic intensification in Spanish and English communication. Flores-Ferrán examines how intensification is defined as well as the various linguistic features, strategies, and devices we employ to escalate and amplify our oral and written communication. The book builds on a rich body of literature, exploring the conceptualization of linguistic intensification within socio-pragmatics and Persuasion Theory. This book also demonstrates the applicability of intensification in language learning by discussing techniques native speakers use to amplify the illocution of their communication.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3303420&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="34">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3299995">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Gastronomy, Hospitality, and the Future of the Restaurant Industry : Post-COVID-19 Perspectives</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Ana Pinto Borges</au>
            <au>António Lopes de Almeida</au>
            <au>Elvira Pacheco Vieira</au>
            <au>Rui Rosa Dias</au>
            <au>Paula Rodrigues</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781799891482</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799891505</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799891512</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Gastronomy, Hospitality, and the Future of the Restaurant Industry : Post-COVID-19 Perspectives</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Ana Pinto Borges</au>
            <au>António Lopes de Almeida</au>
            <au>Elvira Pacheco Vieira</au>
            <au>Rui Rosa Dias</au>
            <au>Paula Rodrigues</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Industries / Hospitality, Travel &amp; Tourism</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Consumer Behavior</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Food Science / Food Safety &amp; Security</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Hospitality industry</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Food tourism</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">COVID-19 Pandemic, 2020---Economic aspects</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Gastronomic tourism has made remarkable progress within the past decade in both academia and within its own sector. However, many industries have suffered from the COVID-19 pandemic, and food tourism businesses had to take unique precautions for the health and safety of global consumers. Despite the economic turbulence of the COVID-19 pandemic, there are many strategies available for the restaurant industry to thrive. Gastronomy, Hospitality, and the Future of the Restaurant Industry: Post-COVID-19 Perspectives presents the most recent research surrounding food and gastronomy in relation to hospitality and tourism, highlighting emerging themes and different methods of approach. Concretely, it constitutes a timely and relevant compendium of chapters that offers its readers relevant issues in gastronomy and management strategies in the hospitality industry. Covering topics such as food tourism, organic food production, and restaurant communication, this book is an essential resource for managers, business owners, entrepreneurs, consultants, marketing specialists, government officials, libraries, researchers, academicians, educators, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3299995&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="35">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3300003">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Applications of Computational Science in Artificial Intelligence</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Anand Nayyar</au>
            <au>Sandeep Kumar</au>
            <au>Akshat Agrawal</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Computational Intelligence and Robotics (ACIR) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799890126</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799890140</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799890157</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Applications of Computational Science in Artificial Intelligence</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Anand Nayyar</au>
            <au>Sandeep Kumar</au>
            <au>Akshat Agrawal</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Artificial Intelligence / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Artificial Intelligence / Expert Systems</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Artificial Intelligence / Natural Language Processing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Machine learning</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Artificial intelligence</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Computational science, in collaboration with engineering, acts as a bridge between hypothesis and experimentation. It is essential to use computational methods and their applications in order to automate processes as many major industries rely on advanced modeling and simulation. Computational science is inherently interdisciplinary and can be used to identify and evaluate complicated systems, foresee their performance, and enhance procedures and strategies. Applications of Computational Science in Artificial Intelligence delivers technological solutions to improve smart technologies architecture, healthcare, and environmental sustainability. It also provides background on key aspects such as computational solutions, computation framework, smart prediction, and healthcare solutions. Covering a range of topics such as high-performance computing and software infrastructure, this reference work is ideal for software engineers, practitioners, researchers, scholars, academicians, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3300003&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="36">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3299994">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Modern Regulations and Practices for Social and Environmental Accounting</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Teresa Eugénio</au>
            <au>Graça Azevedo</au>
            <au>Ana Fialho</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Finance, Accounting, and Economics (AFAE) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799894100</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799894124</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799894131</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Modern Regulations and Practices for Social and Environmental Accounting</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Teresa Eugénio</au>
            <au>Graça Azevedo</au>
            <au>Ana Fialho</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Accounting / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Business Ethics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / Sustainable Development</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Environmental auditing</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Social accounting</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Sustainable development reporting</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>There has been an increased interest in social and environmental issues in recent years as more consideration is given to the idea of sustainability and social accounting. Social accounting can be considered a straightforward manifestation of corporate enforcement to legitimize, explain, and justify the organization's activities or an ethically desirable component of any well-functioning democracy. Social accounting can also include environmental accounting, which is focused on environmental issues. Additional study is required to better understand the relevancy of social and environmental accounting in today's modern business world. Modern Regulations and Practices for Social and Environmental Accounting discusses social and environmental accounting and considers regulations, norms, organizational practices, and the challenges of education. Covering a range of topics such as non-financial reporting and corporate social responsibility, this reference work is ideal for industry professionals, researchers, academicians, managers, practitioners, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3299994&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="37">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3299998">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Cybersecurity Crisis Management and Lessons Learned From the COVID-19 Pandemic</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Ryma Abassi</au>
            <au>Aida Ben Chehida Douss</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Information Security, Privacy, and Ethics (AISPE) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799891642</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799891666</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799891673</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Cybersecurity Crisis Management and Lessons Learned From the COVID-19 Pandemic</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Ryma Abassi</au>
            <au>Aida Ben Chehida Douss</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Security / Network Security</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Security / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">POLITICAL SCIENCE / Security (National &amp; International)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Confidential communications--Physicians</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Privacy, Right of</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Computer networks--Security measures</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Medical records--Access control</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Computer crimes--Prevention</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">COVID-19 Pandemic, 2020---Influence</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Telecommuting</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The COVID-19 pandemic has forced organizations and individuals to embrace new practices such as social distancing and remote working. During these unprecedented times, many have increasingly relied on the internet for work, shopping, and healthcare. However, while the world focuses on the health and economic threats posed by the COVID-19 pandemic, cyber criminals are capitalizing on this crisis as the world has become more digitally dependent and vulnerable than ever. Cybersecurity Crisis Management and Lessons Learned From the COVID-19 Pandemic provides cutting-edge research on the best guidelines for preventing, detecting, and responding to cyber threats within educational, business, health, and governmental organizations during the COVID-19 pandemic. It further highlights the importance of focusing on cybersecurity within organizational crisis management. Covering topics such as privacy and healthcare, remote work, and personal health data, this premier reference source is an indispensable resource for startup companies, health and business executives, ICT procurement managers, IT professionals, libraries, students and educators of higher education, entrepreneurs, government officials, social media experts, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3299998&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="38">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3300001">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Interdisciplinary and Practical Approaches to Managerial Education and Training</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Luísa Cagica Carvalho</au>
            <au>Nuno Teixeira</au>
            <au>Pedro Pardal</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781799882398</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799882411</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799882428</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Interdisciplinary and Practical Approaches to Managerial Education and Training</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Luísa Cagica Carvalho</au>
            <au>Nuno Teixeira</au>
            <au>Pedro Pardal</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Management Science</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">EDUCATION / Teaching / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Executives--Training of</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Business education</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Management--Study and teaching</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>In the last decades, the development of innovative practices has gained considerable interest. New generations of students have grown up in a very different environment from their predecessors, one influenced by information and communications technology (ICT). In a globalized world, ICT is changing the way businesses create and capture value, how and where we work, and how we interact and communicate. Thus, some of the traditional teaching methods are rapidly becoming obsolete and unattractive to the new generation of students. Despite the increase in the development of new teaching approaches in recent years, relevant questions related to learning objectives, suitable methodologies, and impact assessment remain unanswered. Interdisciplinary and Practical Approaches to Managerial Education and Training addresses the best practices, laboratory methods, policies, protocols, and practical approaches to managerial education and training. Covering a wide range of topics such as training programs, teacher education, and online learning, it is ideal for academics, university teachers, researchers, students, public and private institutions, and professionals in managerial training education.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3300001&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="39">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3300000">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Organizational Sustainability in Turbulent Economies</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Rafael Ignacio Perez-Uribe</au>
            <au>Carlos Salcedo-Perez</au>
            <au>Andres Carvajal-Contreras</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Practice, Progress, and Proficiency in Sustainability (PPPS) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799893011</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799893028</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799893035</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Business Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Organizational Sustainability in Turbulent Economies</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Rafael Ignacio Perez-Uribe</au>
            <au>Carlos Salcedo-Perez</au>
            <au>Andres Carvajal-Contreras</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / Sustainable Development</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / Business Development</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Economics / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Strategic planning</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Industrial management</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Social responsibility of business</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Organizational change</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Organizational sustainability and uncertain economies are key topics for modern organizations. New, updated knowledge about such matters is necessary for companies to ensure they are sufficiently prepared for future crises. Additional research is required in this area as the overall amount of material available is below par. The Handbook of Research on Organizational Sustainability in Turbulent Economies provides theoretical and practical evidence that demonstrates how the integration, adaptation, construction, and application of strategic models, methods, and tools can promote organizational sustainability for economies in situations of uncertainty. Covering topics such as work engagement and sustainable development goals, this major reference work is ideal for academicians, practitioners, policymakers, entrepreneurs, business owners, researchers, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3300000&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="40">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3299999">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Cyber Law, Data Protection, and Privacy</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Nisha Dhanraj Dewani</au>
            <au>Zubair Ahmed Khan</au>
            <au>Aarushi Agarwal</au>
            <au>Mamta Sharma</au>
            <au>Shaharyar Asaf Khan</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781799886419</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799886433</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799886440</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Cyber Law, Data Protection, and Privacy</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Nisha Dhanraj Dewani</au>
            <au>Zubair Ahmed Khan</au>
            <au>Aarushi Agarwal</au>
            <au>Mamta Sharma</au>
            <au>Shaharyar Asaf Khan</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Security / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Security / Network Security</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TRUE CRIME / Cybercrime</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Internet--Law and legislation</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Computer crimes--Law and legislation</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Data protection--Law and legislation</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The advancement of information and communication technology has led to a multi-dimensional impact in the areas of law, regulation, and governance. Many countries have declared data protection a fundamental right and established reforms of data protection law aimed at modernizing the global regulatory framework. Due to these advancements in policy, the legal domain has to face many challenges at a rapid pace making it essential to study and discuss policies and laws that regulate and monitor these activities and anticipate new laws that should be implemented in order to protect users. The Handbook of Research on Cyber Law, Data Protection, and Privacy focuses acutely on the complex relationships of technology and law both in terms of substantive legal responses to legal, social, and ethical issues arising in connection with growing public engagement with technology and the procedural impacts and transformative potential of technology on traditional and emerging forms of dispute resolution. Covering a range of topics such as artificial intelligence, data protection, and social media, this major reference work is ideal for government officials, policymakers, industry professionals, academicians, scholars, researchers, practitioners, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3299999&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="41">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3299996">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Design, Deployment, Automation, and Testing Strategies for 6G Mobile Core Network</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>D. Satish Kumar</au>
            <au>G. Prabhakar</au>
            <au>R. Anand</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781799896364</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896388</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896395</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, Pennsylvania [701 E. Chocolate Avenue, Hershey, Pennsylvania, 17033, USA]</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Design, Deployment, Automation, and Testing Strategies for 6G Mobile Core Network</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>D. Satish Kumar</au>
            <au>G. Prabhakar</au>
            <au>R. Anand</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Mobile &amp; Wireless Communications</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Telecommunications</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Data Transmission Systems / Broadband</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Wireless communication systems--Industrial applications</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Wireless communication systems--Technological innovations</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Wireless communication systems--Forecasting</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>To overcome the constraints of 5G for supporting new challenges, 6G wireless systems must be developed with new and attractive features. These systems are expected to increase performance and maximize quality of service several folds more than 5G along with other exciting features. However, 6G is still in its infancy and must be explored. The Handbook of Research on Design, Deployment, Automation, and Testing Strategies for 6G Mobile Core Network discusses the technological feats used in the new 6G wireless systems. It discusses the design, automation, and uses for industry as well as testing strategies. Covering topics such as 6G architecture, smart healthcare, and wireless communication, this major reference work is an excellent resource for computer scientists, engineers, students and professors in higher education, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3299996&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="42">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3299989">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Tribology in Coatings and Surface Treatment</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Amirhossein Pakseresht</au>
            <au>Omid Sharifahmadian</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Chemical and Materials Engineering (ACME) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799896838</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896852</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896869</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Tribology in Coatings and Surface Treatment</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Amirhossein Pakseresht</au>
            <au>Omid Sharifahmadian</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Tribology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Materials Science / Thin Films, Surfaces &amp; Interfaces</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Coatings</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Contact mechanics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Surfaces (Technology)</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Tribology</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Advances are continuously being made in applying the coatings and surface treatments by different techniques to reduce the damages from tribology. Engineers need more detailed information to compare the capability of each coating process in wear resistant and lubrication applications. It is also important to focus on the concepts of tribology in various applications such as the manufacturing process, bio implants, machine elements, and corrosive environments. The need for a comprehensive resource addressing these findings in order to improve wear resistance is unavoidable. The Handbook of Research on Tribology in Coatings and Surface Treatment evaluates the latest advances the fabrication of wear-resistant and lubricant coatings by different techniques and investigates wear-resistant coatings and surface treatments in various applications such as the automobile industry. Covering a wide range of topics such as lubricant coatings and wearable electronic devices, it is ideal for engineers, industry professionals, researchers, academicians, scholars, practitioners, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3299989&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="43">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3299993">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Big Data Analytics and Artificial Intelligence in the Healthcare Industry</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>José Machado</au>
            <au>Hugo Peixoto</au>
            <au>Regina Sousa</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Medical Technologies and Clinical Practice (AMTCP) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799891727</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799891734</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799891741</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Medical Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Big Data Analytics and Artificial Intelligence in the Healthcare Industry</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>José Machado</au>
            <au>Hugo Peixoto</au>
            <au>Regina Sousa</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Artificial Intelligence / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">COMPUTERS / Data Science / Data Analytics</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Informatics</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Artificial intelligence</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Developing new approaches and reliable enabling technologies in the healthcare industry is needed to enhance our overall quality of life and lead to a healthier, innovative, and secure society. Further study is required to ensure these current technologies, such as big data analytics and artificial intelligence, are utilized to their utmost potential and are appropriately applied to advance society. Big Data Analytics and Artificial Intelligence in the Healthcare Industry discusses technologies and emerging topics regarding reliable and innovative solutions applied to the healthcare industry and considers various applications, challenges, and issues of big data and artificial intelligence for enhancing our quality of life. Covering a range of topics such as electronic health records, machine learning, and e-health, this reference work is ideal for healthcare professionals, computer scientists, data analysts, researchers, practitioners, scholars, academicians, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3299993&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="44">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3288261">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Neuroscience for Dentistry</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Barbara J. O'Kane</au>
            <au>Laura C. Barritt</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781626237810</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781626237827</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781638535201</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Thieme</pub>
          <place>New York</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Neuroscience for Dentistry</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Barbara J. O'Kane</au>
            <au>Laura C. Barritt</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Dentistry / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Education &amp; Training</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">MEDICAL / Neuroscience</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Orofacial pain</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Neurosciences</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Dentistry</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>A practical, reader-friendly guide for dental students on the neuroscience of the orofacial regionUnderstanding neural mechanisms that control orofacial pain, proper masticatory function, taste, speech, swallowing, and proprioceptive input to the temporomandibular joint and teeth is an important facet of dentistry. Neuroscience of Dentistry by renowned educators Barbara J. O'Kane and Laura C. Barritt provides foundational knowledge on these topics. The text integrates fundamental concepts of general neuroscience with vital information on neural mechanisms of the orofacial region and associated pain pathways.The book is organized in two parts covering basic neuroscience and orofacial neuroscience. Part one is subdivided into four units on the central nervous system, brain and spinal cord gross anatomy, sensory systems, and motor systems. Part two features three units focused on orofacial structures and tissues, dental structures, and orofacial pain and anesthesia. Each generously illustrated, succinctly written, and consistently formatted chapter includes an introductory overview and learning objectives.Key HighlightsThroughout the book, relevant clinical correlations emphasize the relationship between basic neuroscience and clinical practiceConcise, high-yield illustrations, schematics, charts, and tables enhance understanding of general and orofacial neuroanatomy conceptsHelpful overviews at the beginning of each chapter highlight key conceptsNational board style questions at the end of each chapter emphasize board-relevant information that enables self-studyThis is a must-have resource for dental students taking neuroscience during their first or second year of dental school. It will also benefit other health science and dental hygiene students, as well as oral and maxillofacial surgery residents.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3288261&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="45">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3286798">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Handbook of Research on Green Technologies for Sustainable Management of Agricultural Resources</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>R.S. Sengar</au>
            <au>Reshu Chaudhary</au>
            <au>H.S. Bhadauriya</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Advances in Environmental Engineering and Green Technologies (AEEGT) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799884347</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799884354</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799884361</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Handbook of Research on Green Technologies for Sustainable Management of Agricultural Resources</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>R.S. Sengar</au>
            <au>Reshu Chaudhary</au>
            <au>H.S. Bhadauriya</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Agriculture / Sustainable Agriculture</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Agriculture / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Environmental / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Sustainable agriculture</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Green technology is focused on devising environmentally-friendly (eco-friendly) agricultural practices. It plays a crucial role in dealing with food security issues and reducing the carbon footprint. Green technologies and environmental sustainability are focused on the goals of green technologies, which are becoming increasingly important for ensuring sustainability. The Handbook of Research on Green Technologies for Sustainable Management of Agricultural Resources covers the applications of green technology as well as different eco-friendly technologies for the sustainable management of natural resources. It also explores the timely topic of enhancing crop productivity. It is ideal for agriculturists, farmers, botanists, technologists, policymakers, scientists, academicians, researchers, and students as it covers a variety of concepts such as organic farming and the role of green technologies.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3286798&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="46">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3286799">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Technological Development and Impact on Economic and Environmental Sustainability</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Yilmaz Bayar</au>
            <au>Mahmut Unsal Sasmaz</au>
            <au>Omer Faruk Ozturk</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Practice, Progress, and Proficiency in Sustainability (PPPS) Book Series</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9781799896487</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896500</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781799896517</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Engineering Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey PA</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Technological Development and Impact on Economic and Environmental Sustainability</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Yilmaz Bayar</au>
            <au>Mahmut Unsal Sasmaz</au>
            <au>Omer Faruk Ozturk</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Development / Sustainable Development</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Economics / General</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">NATURE / Environmental Conservation &amp; Protection</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Technological innovations--Environmental aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Technological innovations--Economic aspects</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Sustainable development--Technological innovations</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The globalized world has experienced significant improvements in production and consumption in a heterogeneous way since the industrial revolution. However, the considerable environmental degradation and energy wars resulting from the limited fossil energy sources brought the issue of sustainable development to the world agenda. Sustainable development has become one of the most discussed issues at country and international levels and requires further investigation to fully understand how we can move towards a more sustainable future. Technological Development and Impact on Economic and Environmental Sustainability explores the determinants of economic, social, and environmental sustainability from a multidisciplinary perspective in the globalized world, analyzes the impacts of applied sustainable policies, and considers the improvements in the Sustainable Development Goals. Covering topics such as economic growth and climate change, this reference work is ideal for researchers, academicians, scholars, practitioners, industry professionals, instructors, and students.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3286799&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="47">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3286797">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Disciplinary Literacy As a Support for Culturally and Linguistically Responsive Teaching and Learning</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Leslie Haas</au>
            <au>Jill T. Tussey</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9781668442159</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668442166</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9781668442173</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>Information Science Reference</pub>
          <place>Hershey, Pennsylvania [701 E. Chocolate Avenue, Hershey, Pennsylvania, 17033, USA]</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Disciplinary Literacy As a Support for Culturally and Linguistically Responsive Teaching and Learning</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Leslie Haas</au>
            <au>Jill T. Tussey</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Literacy</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">EDUCATION / Multicultural Education</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Multicultural education</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Culturally relevant pedagogy</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Inclusive education</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>All students deserve inclusive and engaging learning experiences. Opportunities for student growth and environments that honor culture and language are essential in a modern society that promotes inclusivity. Thoughtful disciplinary literacy practices offer embedded opportunities across grade levels and content areas to support inclusive classroom cultures. Therefore, the value of culturally and linguistically responsive pedagogy, supported through literacy experiences, should not be underestimated and should become a priority within K-12 education. Disciplinary Literacy as a Support for Culturally and Linguistically Responsive Teaching and Learning develops a conceptual framework and pedagogical support for disciplinary literacy practices related to culturally and linguistically responsive teaching and learning. It presents a variety of research and practice protocols supporting student success through explored connections between disciplinary literacy and inclusive pedagogical practices. Covering topics such as cultural awareness, racialized text, and gender identity development, this premier reference source is an indispensable resource for pre-service teachers, educators of K-12 and higher education, educational administration, government officials, curriculum directors, literacy professionals, professional development coordinators, teacher preparation programs, libraries, researchers, and academicians.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3286797&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="48">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3286329">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Financial Accounting : Introduction to German GAAP with Exercises</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Robert Nothhelfer</au>
          </aug>
          <isbn type="print">9783110744125</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110744170</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110744248</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <ed>2nd Edition</ed>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Financial Accounting : Introduction to German GAAP with Exercises</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Robert Nothhelfer</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMICS / Accounting / Financial</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Accounting--Germany</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Accounting--Standards--Germany</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>Every German student of business administration needs to have a basic understanding of accounting according to German GAAP. Thanks to globalization, many courses in German accounting are nowadays conducted in English. In addition, many foreign subsidiaries of German companies have to prepare their part of consolidated financial statements according to German GAAP. So far students taking these accounting courses and professionals preparing these financial statements have had to rely on German literature only and did not have an English textbook to refer to that covers German GAAP accounting topics in detail. To fill this gap, the first edition of this book offered a compact introduction to financial statements according to German GAAP, and exercises on individual topics with solutions and case studies for in-depth and effective learning. The revised and extended second edition with updated references and text, adds a complete translation of the parts of the German Commercial Code that are directly relevant for accounting. Students and professionals can now go back to the original source when working out accounting problems. It provides ideal support for German-speaking students and is furthermore valuable for professionals looking for explanations when preparing the data for consolidated financial statements. Includes exercises and case studies for practice Ideal textbook for students of German universities attending English-speaking lectures in financial management Ideal introduction for professionals with succinct explanations and additional support in the form of a glossary and list of vocabulary terms</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3286329&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="49">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3286322">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Environmental and Biochemical Toxicology : Concepts, Case Studies and Challenges</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Jürgen Gailer</au>
            <au>Raymond J. Turner</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>De Gruyter Graduate</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110626247</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110626285</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110626346</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <pub>De Gruyter</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Environmental and Biochemical Toxicology : Concepts, Case Studies and Challenges</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Jürgen Gailer</au>
            <au>Raymond J. Turner</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Environmental</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Biochemistry</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Life Sciences / Ecology</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Environmental Science</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Chemical &amp; Biochemical</subj>
            <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Chemistry / Toxicology</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Biochemical toxicology--Case studies</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Environmental toxicology--Case studies</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>This text coherently links biochemical fundamentals and mechanisms with economic and societal problems of environmental pollution. It addresses interdisciplinary topics such as regulatory problems, sampling and pollutant quantifi cation, model organisms and provides a philosophical perspective on the toxin load on a variety of organisms, including humans in the environment in the Anthropocene. Case studies and exercises illustrate current issues and discuss future aspects.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3286322&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
  <rec resultID="50">
    <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="3286328">
      <controlInfo>
        <bkinfo>
          <btl>Number in the World's Languages : A Comparative Handbook</btl>
          <aug>
            <au>Paolo Acquaviva</au>
            <au>Michael Daniel</au>
          </aug>
          <sertl>Comparative Handbooks of Linguistics</sertl>
          <isbn type="print">9783110560695</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110619546</isbn>
          <isbn type="electronic">9783110622713</isbn>
        </bkinfo>
        <pubinfo>
          <dt year="2022" month="01" day="01"></dt>
          <vid>00005</vid>
          <pub>De Gruyter Mouton</pub>
          <place>Berlin</place>
        </pubinfo>
        <artinfo>
          <formats>
            <fmt type="" />
          </formats>
          <tig>
            <atl>Number in the World's Languages : A Comparative Handbook</atl>
          </tig>
          <aug>
            <au>Paolo Acquaviva</au>
            <au>Michael Daniel</au>
          </aug>
          <sug>
            <subj type="bisac">LANGUAGE ARTS &amp; DISCIPLINES / Linguistics / General</subj>
            <subj type="unclass">Grammar, Comparative and general--Number</subj>
          </sug>
          <ab>The strong development in research on grammatical number in recent years has created a need for a unified perspective. The different frameworks, the ramifications of the theoretical questions, and the diversity of phenomena across typological systems, make this a significant challenge. This book addresses the challenge with a series of in-depth analyses of number across a typologically diverse sample, unified by a common set of descriptive and analytic questions from a semantic, morphological, syntactic, and discourse perspective. Each case study is devoted to a single language, or in a few cases to a language group. They are written by specialists who can rely on first-hand data or on material of difficult access, and can place the phenomena in the context of the respective system. The studies are preceded and concluded by critical overviews which frame the discussion and identify the main results and open questions. With specialist chapters breaking new ground, this book will help number specialists relate their results to other theoretical and empirical domains, and it will provide a reliable guide to all linguists and other researchers interested in number.</ab>
          <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
          <doctype>Book</doctype>
        </artinfo>
        <language code="eng">English</language>
      </controlInfo>
      <displayInfo>
        <pLink>
          <url>https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=3286328&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
        </pLink>
      </displayInfo>
    </header>
  </rec>
</records>